<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<trainFigures>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-227X-7-11-5</ID>
<CLASS>DRAN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Success of microvascular surgery; repair mesenteric injury and prevent short bowel syndrome: a case report Mesenteric angiography performed on the postoperative first month. The arrow shows the anastomosis between the arteries.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-230X-10-117-4</ID>
<CLASS>DRAN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Refractory obstructive jaundice in a child affected with thalassodrepanocytosis: a new endoscopic approach Cholangiography after stent removal, showing resolutiom of biliary angle, no filling defects, and good biliary drainage .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2342-3-2-3</ID>
<CLASS>DRAN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Angiographic findings and clinical implications of persistent primitive hypoglossal artery Catheterisation of the right vertebral artery, which appears hypoplastic.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2342-6-3-1</ID>
<CLASS>DRAN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Percutaneous subclavian artery stent-graft placement following failed ultrasound guided subclavian venous access Right innominate artery angiography in right anterior oblique (RAO) 65 degree obliquity. The subclavian sheath is opacified with a small amount of contrast within the lumen of this device (white arrow). The image demonstrates the ventral, proximal entry point of the sheath into the subclavian artery (black arrow).</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2482-11-14-2</ID>
<CLASS>DRAN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Severe gastric variceal haemorrhage due to splenic artery thrombosis and consecutive arterial bypass Angiography of the the coeliac trunc (1) showing the common hepatic artery (2) and the left gastric artery with multiple collateral vessels (3) . The splenic artery as third branch is missing. Residual of N-butyl-2-cyanoacrylate lipiodol injection (4) can be seen.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2482-7-18-3</ID>
<CLASS>DRAN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Cavo-portal transposition in rat: a new simple model Selective mesenteric vein angiography after cavo-portal transposition: splanchnic flow is shunted to the vena cava system through the neo-formed porto-caval shunts. smv = superior mesenteric vein, spv = splenic vein, icv = intercostal veins, itv = internal thoracic vein, tev = thoraco-epigastric vein, sev = superficial epigastric vein.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2482-7-4-1</ID>
<CLASS>DRAN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Peroneal artery pseudoaneurysm  –  a case report and literature review Distal subtraction angiogram shows a distal peroneal pseudoaneurysm and a mid peroneal aneurysmal dilatation.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2482-9-7-2</ID>
<CLASS>DRAN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Intraoperative angiography should be standard in cerebral aneurysm surgery Intraoperative angiogram demonstrating occlusion of middle cerebral artery aneurysm with patency of middle cerebral branches . The anterior communicating artery aneurysm is also occluded, but there is no filling of the anterior cerebral artery, suggesting parent vessel occlusion by the clip.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1476-7120-1-16-3</ID>
<CLASS>DRAN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Imaging of all three coronary arteries by transthoracic echocardiography. an illustrated guide Angiography of the left coronary artery in left antero-oblique (LAO) projection with caudal angulation. Division of left circumflex (Cx) coronary artery into segments: proximal (P) and middle (M)</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1476-7120-1-16-35</ID>
<CLASS>DRAN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Imaging of all three coronary arteries by transthoracic echocardiography. an illustrated guide Angiography of the right coronary artery in LAO projection. Spacial relations between ultrasound transducer located in subcostal position and the middle segment of the right coronary artery (encircled in red) are shown</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1476-7120-2-1-3</ID>
<CLASS>DRAN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>A comparison of Power Doppler with conventional sonographic imaging for the evaluation of renal artery stenosis Selective angiography of a stenosis of right RA.  This image has been obtained from the same patient of figure  2  at the time of percutaneous angioplasty. The stenosis of the right RA is evident.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1476-7120-2-13-3</ID>
<CLASS>DRAN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Atypical vessels as an early sign of intracardiac myxoma? Right coronary artery (baseline) in 90 degree LAO projection. White arrow = atypical vessels in the interatrial septum</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1476-7120-6-48-6</ID>
<CLASS>DRAN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Effort angina in a patient with advanced coronary artery disease. Role played by coronary angiography, Ivus and cardiac CT: case report Coronary angiography image (60 °  left anterior oblique angle) obtained at the six-month follow-up shows 70% diameter stenosis in the second segment of the right coronary artery (arrow).</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1476-7120-6-48-7</ID>
<CLASS>DRAN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Effort angina in a patient with advanced coronary artery disease. Role played by coronary angiography, Ivus and cardiac CT: case report Coronary angiography image (30 °  right anterior oblique angle) obtained at the six-month follow-up shows 70% diameter stenosis in the second segment of the obtuse marginal branch (arrow).</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1476-7120-6-48-9</ID>
<CLASS>DRAN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Effort angina in a patient with advanced coronary artery disease. Role played by coronary angiography, Ivus and cardiac CT: case report Coronary angiography image obtained just after stent placement in the right coronary artery showing the good revascularization of the artery.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1477-9560-7-1-1</ID>
<CLASS>DRAN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Non ST-segment elevation myocardial infarction in patient with essential thrombocythemia Coronary angiography revealing thrombus-like filling defect in the mid portion of RCA .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1748-7161-2-4-2</ID>
<CLASS>DRAN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>High pressures and asymmetrical stresses in the scoliotic disc in the absence of muscle loading Part of intraoperative representative radiograph showing electrodes and pressure transducer inserted from the convex side of the scoliotic curve (same patient as figure 1).</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1749-7221-3-9-2</ID>
<CLASS>DRAN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Axillary artery injury combined with delayed brachial plexus palsy due to compressive hematoma in a young patient: a case report Selective digital subtraction angiography of the axillary artery . The axillary artery was completely occluded at the site of the coracoid process of the scapula, and collateral flow through the thoracoacromial (*) and the posterior circumflex humeral ( † ) arteries existed.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1749-7922-2-1-10</ID>
<CLASS>DRAN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>State of the art: noninvasive imaging and management of neurovascular trauma 25-year old woman involved in a rollover motor vehicle collision. On admission to the hospital, a screening four-vessel angiogram revealed a pseudoaneurysm of the left vertebral artery at the level of the C1 – C2 disc space. Follow-up angiography performed 7 days later revealed enlargement of the pseudoaneurysm and concomitant narrowing of the vertebral artery. Due to the tortuosity of the vertebral artery, stent placement was not deemed a viable option and the vertebral artery was embolized. Lateral digital subtraction angiogram, left vertebral artery. Notice the pseudoaneurysm arising from the distal vertebral artery (arrow), and the adjacent vertebral artery narrowing.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1749-7922-2-1-11</ID>
<CLASS>DRAN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>State of the art: noninvasive imaging and management of neurovascular trauma 25-year old woman involved in a rollover motor vehicle collision. On admission to the hospital, a screening four-vessel angiogram revealed a pseudoaneurysm of the left vertebral artery at the level of the C1 – C2 disc space. Follow-up angiography performed 7 days later revealed enlargement of the pseudoaneurysm and concomitant narrowing of the vertebral artery. Due to the tortuosity of the vertebral artery, stent placement was not deemed a viable option and the vertebral artery was embolized. Unsubtracted image demonstrating coils placed distal and proximal to the pseudoaneurysm, trapping the diseased segment of vessel.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1749-7922-2-1-12</ID>
<CLASS>DRAN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>State of the art: noninvasive imaging and management of neurovascular trauma 25-year old woman involved in a rollover motor vehicle collision. On admission to the hospital, a screening four-vessel angiogram revealed a pseudoaneurysm of the left vertebral artery at the level of the C1 – C2 disc space. Follow-up angiography performed 7 days later revealed enlargement of the pseudoaneurysm and concomitant narrowing of the vertebral artery. Due to the tortuosity of the vertebral artery, stent placement was not deemed a viable option and the vertebral artery was embolized. Post-embolization anteroposterior digital subtraction angiogram, right vertebral artery. There is normal filling of the basilar artery, and reflux of contrast into the distal left vertebral artery which fills the left posterior inferior cerebellar artery (arrow). Images courtesy of Guido Scatorchia, MD.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1749-7922-2-1-7</ID>
<CLASS>DRAN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>State of the art: noninvasive imaging and management of neurovascular trauma 36-year old woman, s/p motor vehicle collision. On admission, an angiogram demonstrated a pseudoaneurysm of the thoracic aorta, as well as a grade 3 (pseudoaneurysm) of her left internal carotid artery. Her aorta was repaired immediately; on follow-up angiography of her carotid injury, her pseudoaneurysm had progressed and there was significant narrowing of the adjacent internal carotid artery. Digital subtraction angiogram of the left internal carotid artery, 7-days following initial injury. There is a pseudoaneurysm (arrow) of the proximal internal carotid artery with narrowing of the adjacent artery. A second, smaller pseudoaneurysm (arrowhead) is noted in the more distal artery.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1749-7922-2-1-8</ID>
<CLASS>DRAN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>State of the art: noninvasive imaging and management of neurovascular trauma 36-year old woman, s/p motor vehicle collision. On admission, an angiogram demonstrated a pseudoaneurysm of the thoracic aorta, as well as a grade 3 (pseudoaneurysm) of her left internal carotid artery. Her aorta was repaired immediately; on follow-up angiography of her carotid injury, her pseudoaneurysm had progressed and there was significant narrowing of the adjacent internal carotid artery. Digital subtraction angiogram of the left internal carotid artery, s/p stent placement. A 6 mm  ×  47 mm Magic Wallstent (Boston Scientific, Watertown, MA) was placed. Notice the immediate and nearly complete resolution of the pseudoaneurysms.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1749-7922-4-14-1</ID>
<CLASS>DRAN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Coronary artery dissection and acute myocardial infarction following blunt chest trauma Coronary angiogram showing dissection of the middle part of the left anterior descending coronary artery (arrow) .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1749-7922-4-39-2</ID>
<CLASS>DRAN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Lateral abdominal wall hematoma as a rare complication after carotid artery stenting: a case report Emergent selective angiography of the external iliac artery shows active bleeding from the right superficial circumflex iliac artery (arrow) . Transcatheter arterial embolization with Gelfoam and microcoils was performed successfully.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1749-8090-1-30-1</ID>
<CLASS>DRAN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Repeated successful surgical rescues of early and delayed multiple ruptures of ventricular septum, right ventricle and aneurysmal left ventricle following massive biventricular infarction Left coronary angiogram (LAO view) showing occluded LAD.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1749-8090-3-19-1</ID>
<CLASS>DRAN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Large asymptomatic Left Atrial Myxoma with ossification: case report Coronary angiography . Coronary angiography, white arrow denote major atrial branch of the right coronary artery supplying the left atrial tumor mass, marked neovascularity with clusters of tortuous vessels, and blood pooling (light arrow).</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1749-8090-3-33-1</ID>
<CLASS>DRAN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Anomalous origin of the left coronary artery from the pulmonary artery (ALCAPA) presenting with ventricular fibrillation in an adult: a case report Coronary angiography . Coronary angiography of the right coronary artery with collateral filling of the left coronary vascular territory, which connects directly to the pulmonary trunk.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1750-1172-2-28-1</ID>
<CLASS>DRAN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Fibromuscular dysplasia The "string-of-beads" feature in medial fibromuscular dysplasia . The sign is caused by areas of relative stenoses alternating with small aneurysms. The diameters of the aneurysms exceed the normal diameter of the artery. The sign is characteristic of medial FMD. A similar bead appearance may be seen in perimedial FMD, but the diameters of the beads do not exceed the normal diameter of the artery [10]. Note the involvement of branch renal arteries.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1750-1172-4-17-2</ID>
<CLASS>DRAN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Patent arterial duct Lateral angiogram demonstrating a large tubular type duct (type C) with aortic (AO) to pulmonary flow (MPA) . The catheter can be seen entering the MPA from the right ventricle, a second pigtail catheter is positioned in the descending aorta from which contrast is delivered.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1752-1947-0003-0000008389-4</ID>
<CLASS>DRAN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Distal migration of a floating carotid thrombus in a patient using oral contraceptives: a case report Total occlusion of the horizontal portion of the left middle cerebral artery is clear on emergent cerebral angiogram .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1752-1947-1-125-1</ID>
<CLASS>DRAN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Sphenopalatine-sphenopalatine anastomosis: a unique cause of intractable epistaxis, safely treated with microcatheter embolization: a case report Left common carotid artery angiogram demonstrating external carotid ligation.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1752-1947-1-58-1</ID>
<CLASS>DRAN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Fibromuscular dysplasia in an accessory renal artery causing renovascular hypertension: a case report Renal artery angiography in a 35-year-old woman with unexplained hypertension showing the typical "string-of-beads" sign (arrows) characteristic for FMD involving the lower left renal artery (accessory artery). The arrowhead indicates a small saccular aneurysm at the distal portion of right renal artery.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1752-1947-2-392-2</ID>
<CLASS>DRAN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Right subclavian double steal syndrome: a case report Angiography after catheterization of the innominate artery near the origin of the right common carotid and subclavian arteries demonstrating the occlusion of the brachiocephalic trunk (bold black arrow) . Note that contrast media is not running along the right vertebral artery due to the retrograde blood flow in the vessel (subclavian-vertebral steal syndrome). Concomitant stenosis of the common carotid artery (thin black arrow) is a manifestation of the generalized atherosclerotic disease. Stenotic lesions of initial and mid-portion segments in the subclavian artery were not considered to be that significant for acute treatment. In case they progressed we considered endovascular treatment. White arrow: pacemaker wire.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1752-1947-3-44-2</ID>
<CLASS>DRAN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Management of major bile duct injury after laparoscopic cholecystectomy: a case report Percutaneous decompression of both left and right biliary ducts was successful . A false route was created to the duodenum through partial opening of the left duct clip from the guidewire.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1752-1947-3-9292-2</ID>
<CLASS>DRAN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Complete abdominal aortic aneurysm thrombosis and obstruction of both common iliac arteries with intrathrombotic pressures demonstrating a continuing risk of rupture: a case report and review of the literature Digital subtraction angiography demonstrating complete aneurysm thrombosis and obstruction of both common iliac arteries . Level 0: 1 cm above the renal arteries; level 1: 3 cm distal to the renal arteries; level 2: at the origin of the inferior mesentery artery; level 3: 2 cm distal to level 2.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1754-9493-4-13-1</ID>
<CLASS>DRAN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Acute morbidity and complications of thigh compartment syndrome: A report of 26 cases Angiogram of thigh vessels in young female patient on bicycle who was hit by car one hour before admission . She was in hemorrhagic shock, with peripheral pulses and sensation present, with unstable femoral shaft fracture and with clinical presentation of thigh compartment syndrome. Arterial bleed was diagnosed by angiography and damaged arterial brunch was promptly embolized. All three thigh compartments were released, femur fracture was fixed with intramedullary nail and patient had good final outcome.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1757-1626-0002-0000006222-003</ID>
<CLASS>DRAN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Trans-arterial and trans-venous interventional radiology for an elderly patient with life-threatening pelvic injury after accidental falling due to life-threatening cardiac arrhythmia: a case report Pelvic angiography showed multiple contrast medium extravasation (white arrow and white circle).</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1757-1626-0002-0000006222-004</ID>
<CLASS>DRAN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Trans-arterial and trans-venous interventional radiology for an elderly patient with life-threatening pelvic injury after accidental falling due to life-threatening cardiac arrhythmia: a case report After completion of transcatheter arterial embolization, the contrast medium extravasation halted.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1757-1626-0002-0000006266-002</ID>
<CLASS>DRAN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Ureteroiliac fistula: a case report review of the literature Provocative arteriography after stent removal showing the UIF.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1757-1626-0002-0000006351-004</ID>
<CLASS>DRAN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Bilateral renal angiomyolipoma in a patient with tuberous sclerosis treated with resection of one kidney and transarterial embolization of other kidney using CT during selective arteriography: a case report Left renal arteriogram after the embolization procedure angiography performed after the embolization procedure demonstrated satisfactory visualization of the normal renal parenchyma and the remaining embolized tumor vasculature.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1757-1626-0002-0000006374-004</ID>
<CLASS>DRAN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Coronary artery disease mimicking Tako-tsubo cardiomyopathy: a case report A rudimentary RCA was detected to exhibit a 95% occlusion following the right ventricular branch.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1757-1626-0002-0000006562-004</ID>
<CLASS>DRAN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Coil embolization of inferior epigastric artery pseudoaneurysm after percutaneous thrombin injection failure: a case report Selective angiography of the EIA demonstrates IEA pseudoaneurysm (arrow).</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1757-1626-0002-0000006741-003</ID>
<CLASS>DRAN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Coronary steal by left atrial myxoma: a case report Normal Left coronary angiograms without coronary artery fistula after surgery.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1757-1626-0002-0000007992-001</ID>
<CLASS>DRAN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Pleurobiliary fistula, a rare complication of hepatocellular carcinoma after locoregional chemotherapy: a case report Image of endoscopic cholangiography showing the route of the pleurobiliary fistula as well as the distension of the intrahepatic biliary tree.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1757-1626-0002-0000008186-001</ID>
<CLASS>DRAN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Preoperative diagnosis of obscure gastrointestinal bleeding due to a GIST of the jejunum: a case report The superselective catheterization of an ileal artery shows voluminous disorder with abnormal arterial structures and areas of stagnation of the contrast medium.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1757-1626-0002-0000008186-002</ID>
<CLASS>DRAN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Preoperative diagnosis of obscure gastrointestinal bleeding due to a GIST of the jejunum: a case report The parenchymal phase of the superselective catheterization of the same ileal artery shows the full extent of the disorder.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1757-1626-0002-0000008881-1</ID>
<CLASS>DRAN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Renal artery rupture following cutting balloon angioplasty for fibromuscular dysplasia: a case report Abdominal digital subtraction angiography of a 30-year-old female patient presenting with hypertension of recent onset depicts a high-grade stenosis at the trunk of the right renal artery . Note that the lesion has characteristic features of the intimal type of fibromuscular dysplasia.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1757-1626-0002-0000008881-2</ID>
<CLASS>DRAN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Renal artery rupture following cutting balloon angioplasty for fibromuscular dysplasia: a case report Selective right renal artery angiography following dilatation of the lesion with a 5-mm and a 6 mm balloon depicts 50% residual stenosis . The stenosis was accompanied with a 15 mm Hg of systolic pressure gradient.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1757-1626-1-420-4</ID>
<CLASS>DRAN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Bilateral blunt carotid artery trauma associated with a double lower thoracic spine fracture: a case report and review of the literature MR angiography .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1757-1626-2-171-1</ID>
<CLASS>DRAN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Endovascular stenting of traumatic extracranial carotid artery dissections in the pediatric population: a case report 3D reconstructed time-of-flight MRA shows very minimal irregularity of the distal right ICA just below the skull base consistent with a small focal dissection at this site (arrow) .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1757-1626-3-81-2</ID>
<CLASS>DRAN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Acute Subarachnoid Hemorrhage and Cardiac Abnormalities: Takotsubo Cardiomyopathy or Neurogenic Stunned Myocardium? a case report Ruptured basilar fenestration aneurysm off of the right vertebral to basilar artery, 3  ×  3 mm with a 2 mm neck pointing anterior and left .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1757-7241-16-16-2</ID>
<CLASS>DRAN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Vascular injuries after minor blunt upper extremity trauma: pitfalls in the recognition and diagnosis of potential "near miss" injuries Same case as in figure 1. Angiography demonstrates a traumatic axillary artery pseudoaneurysm (arrow).</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1757-7241-17-42-8</ID>
<CLASS>DRAN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Vascular injuries after blunt chest trauma: diagnosis and management Aortogram depicting aortic injury (arrow) with undeployed endovascular graft in position (arrowhead) .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2474-8-17-15</ID>
<CLASS>DRCO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>A musculoskeletal model of low grade connective tissue inflammation in patients with thyroid associated ophthalmopathy (TAO): the WOMED concept of lateral tension and its general implications in disease Metabolic imaging using whole body  18 F-Fluorodeoxyglucose PET and CT. Note the metabolic activity on the lateral side of the left lower limb as well as on the right ankle. The area around the ankle corresponds to the Shen mai acupuncture point which has been evaluated in our study. Shank muscles are commonly more active in locomotion. The image was provided courteously by Dr David Townsend, University of Tennessee [165].</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1477-7800-5-24-2</ID>
<CLASS>DRCO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>A pulmonary mass with invasion into the heart Axial fused PET-CT demonstrating FDG accumulation in a right middle lobe mass.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1477-7819-5-64-3</ID>
<CLASS>DRCO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>FDG-PET scan in patients with clinically and/or radiologically suspicious colorectal cancer recurrence but normal CEA Transaxial, sagittal, and coronal PET/CT fusion images demonstrating a ring-shaped liver lesion (arrow) with increased metabolic activity (SUV max :5.5) surrounding a photopenic center in a patient previously treated with Yittrium-90 microspheres. CEA became positive two months after PET and subsequent pathology demonstrated tumor recurrence as well as nodal metastasis.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1477-7819-5-65-1</ID>
<CLASS>DRCO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>PET probe-guided surgery: applications and clinical protocol FDG-PET/CT scan of a patient with nasopharyngeal cancer. Transverse slice demonstrating FDG-positive primary site</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1477-7819-5-80-2</ID>
<CLASS>DRCO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Combined use of preoperative  18 F FDG-PET imaging and intraoperative gamma probe detection for accurate assessment of tumor recurrence in patients with colorectal cancer PET/CT fusion image on transaxial section demonstrates a hypermetabolic lesion (SUV max  : 8.2, Patient number 14) in the segment 6 of the liver (arrow) which could not be detected by GP. Final pathology was consistent with CRC metastasis.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1477-7819-6-24-2</ID>
<CLASS>DRCO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Substernal oxyphil parathyroid adenoma producing PTHrP with hypercalcemia and normal PTH level Tc-99m-sestamibi Tc-99m sodium pertechnetate substraction image showed an area of intense uptake below the inferior pole of the left thyroid lobe, in the upper mediastinum, in the left median position and normal thyroid with homogenous radiopharmaceutical uptake (arrow).</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1477-7819-7-96-2</ID>
<CLASS>DRCO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Isolated recurrence of distal adenocarcinoma of the extrahepatic bile duct on a draining sinus scar after curative resection: Case Report and review of the literature PET-CT . Isolated recurrence in chest wall of a previously resected cholangiocarcinoma: intense glucose uptake.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1477-7819-9-146-3</ID>
<CLASS>DRCO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>A case of HER-2-positive recurrent breast cancer showing a clinically complete response to trastuzumab-containing chemotherapy after primary treatment of triple-negative breast cancer FDG-PET showed swelling of the left axilla and infraclavicular lymph nodes with FDG accumulation (SUV max 4.5) . No accumulation was observed in other organs, including the left breast.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1477-7819-9-3-3</ID>
<CLASS>DRCO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>An operative case of hepatic pseudolymphoma difficult to differentiate from primary hepatic marginal zone B-cell lymphoma of mucosa-associated lymphoid tissue FDG-PET CT demonstrated the tumor had a high standardized uptake value (SUVmax: 3.6) for FDG . No other site showed FDG uptake, suggesting that liver tumor is not secondary from malignant lesions of other organs.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1532-429X-12-1-1</ID>
<CLASS>DRCO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Cardiovascular magnetic resonance and PET-CT of left atrial paraganglioma Axial view of PET-CT scan image demonstrates a large hypermetabolic mass with intense uptake of F 18  Levo-DOPA in the posterior mediastinum near the left atrium which is consistent with paraganglioma .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1748-717X-1-7-6</ID>
<CLASS>DRCO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>IMRT using simultaneously integrated boost (SIB) in head and neck cancer patients An example of an IMRT isodose plan using simultaneously integrated boost. Depicted is an axial slice, 64 mm above the isocenter of the plan. Contoured are PTV1 (69.6 Gy), PTV2 (60 Gy) and PTV3 (54 Gy), gross tumor volumes of the primary and macroscopic nodal disease, and normal structures (spinal cord, brain, parotid glands, anterior soft tissues, dorsal soft tissues). Note the well-spared spinal cord and parotid glands despite of bilateral nodal disease covered with high doses (nodal and primary gross tumor volumes included into the PTV1).</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1748-717X-3-25-3</ID>
<CLASS>DRCO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>The impact of functional imaging on radiation medicine Advantages of PET/CT in staging Lung cancer . Coronal slice of a PET/CT scan demonstrating a large left lung mass showing peripheral hypermetabolism with central necrosis (olive arrow), positive mediastinal disease, two liver lesions, and previously unsuspected pelvic bone metastases (red arrows). The presence of distant metastases changes the treatment options for the patient.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1748-717X-3-29-2</ID>
<CLASS>DRCO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>FDG-PET/CT imaging for staging and radiotherapy treatment planning of head and neck carcinoma Axial FDG-PET/CT image of a patient with nasopharyngeal undifferentiated carcinoma . The computed tomography gross tumor volume (CT-GTV) and the positron emission tomography (PET)-GTV are highlighted with red and light blue contours, respectively. For treatment purposes both findings were taken into account.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1748-717X-5-10-1</ID>
<CLASS>DRCO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>FDG-PET/CT imaging for staging and target volume delineation in conformal radiotherapy of anal carcinoma PET/CT image in axial view of a T3N2 case . Different colours are used to highlight the contours of the treatment volumes: CT-GTV (blue), PET-GTV (red), PET/CT-GTV (purple), CT-CTV (light blue), and PET/CT-CTV (yellow). The PET/CT GTV and the PET/CT-CTV were used for treatment purposes.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1748-717X-5-5-4</ID>
<CLASS>DRCO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Comparison of T2 and FLAIR imaging for target delineation in high grade gliomas Planning T2 MRI fused with FLAIR images from same date and T1 MRI obtained at time of failure . The failure volume (rGTV) is contoured in light green. The T2 and FLAIR CTVs are outlined in red and cyan respectively. The T2 and FLAIR PTVs are outlined in orange and dark blue respectively. The FLAIR PTV encompasses a greater portion of the failure volume than T2 PTV. Overlay of the 95% dose color wash shows that the failure is central.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1752-1947-3-9290-2</ID>
<CLASS>DRCO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Diagnosis of invasive aspergillus tracheobronchitis facilitated by endobronchial ultrasound-guided transbronchial needle aspiration: a case report PET-CT (positron emission tomography - computer tomography) scan showing FDG-avid circumferential thickening of distal LMS bronchus and left upper lobe (SUV of 7.4) .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1752-1947-4-320-1</ID>
<CLASS>DRCO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Neuroendocrine carcinoma of the seminal vesicles presenting with Lambert Eaton syndrome: a case report PET-CT scan, January 2008: Strong accumulation in projection to the right seminal vesicle and the right parailiacal lymph nodes .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1752-1947-4-320-2</ID>
<CLASS>DRCO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Neuroendocrine carcinoma of the seminal vesicles presenting with Lambert Eaton syndrome: a case report PET-CT scan, August 2008: declining accumulation in projection to the right seminal vesicle and the right parailiacal lymph nodes .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1752-1947-5-223-3</ID>
<CLASS>DRCO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Metastasis of a cecal adenocarcinoma to the prostate five years after a right hemicolectomy: a case report Fused positron emission tomography-computed tomography (PET-CT) cross-sectional image demonstrating prostatic metastasis with central necrosis .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1752-1947-5-342-2</ID>
<CLASS>DRCO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Intramedullary spinal cord metastasis from colonic carcinoma presenting as Brown-S é quard syndrome: a case report Sagittal fused PET-CT scan of his cervical spine showing a small focus of intense tracer uptake in the spinal canal at C2-C3 level in his neck .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1752-1947-5-342-3</ID>
<CLASS>DRCO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Intramedullary spinal cord metastasis from colonic carcinoma presenting as Brown-S é quard syndrome: a case report Axial fused PET-CT scan of the cervical spine showing a small focus of intense tracer uptake in the spinal canal at C2-C3 level in the neck .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1752-1947-5-483-1</ID>
<CLASS>DRCO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Efficacy of sorafenib, a multi-tyrosine kinase inhibitor, in an adenoid cystic carcinoma metastatic to the lung: case report and review of literature PET/CT scan demonstrating metastatic disease before any systemic therapy was initiated .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-230X-10-2-5</ID>
<CLASS>DRCT</CLASS>
<CAPTION>The clinical presentations of ectopic biliary drainage into duodenal bulbus and stomach with a thorough review of the current literature CT appearance . Pneumobilia in CT.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2342-2-1-6</ID>
<CLASS>DRCT</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Endovascular treatment of huge saccular abdominal aortic aneurysm in a young Behcet patient: mid-term result A, B. Control abdominal CT image after 18 months shows a decrease in the size of the aneurysm sac and patency of the stent graft. No endoleak was noted.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2407-4-89-1</ID>
<CLASS>DRCT</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Atypical presentation of hepatocellular carcinoma: a mass on the left thoracic wall Thoracic computerized tomography showing a lesion of 7 cm  ×  6.5 cm in diameter on the left anterolateral chest wall in the left axillary region at the level of 4. – 5. ribs with minimal compressive atelectasis and destruction of the ribs.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2407-6-244-1</ID>
<CLASS>DRCT</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Ciliated hepatic foregut cyst in a patient with renal cell carcinoma CT scan showing the renal mass.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2482-10-30-1</ID>
<CLASS>DRCT</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Swordfish bill injury involving abdomen and vertebral column: case report and review Abdominal computed tomography scan on admission, demonstrating a penetrating foreign body .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2482-4-8-1</ID>
<CLASS>DRCT</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Modified capitonage in partial cystectomy performed for liver hydatid disease: Report of 2 cases Abdominal CT scan demonstrating a large right lobe hydatid cyst. You can also see the daughter cysts that are contained in the hydatid cyst. In the present slice the cyst's dimensions are 5  ×  7 cm. The real size of the cyst as it was estimated in other slices estimated to 15  ×  12 cm</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2482-5-4-2</ID>
<CLASS>DRCT</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Necrotic gangrenous intrathoracic appendix in a marfanoid adult patient: a case report CT scan of thorax and abdomen demonstrating the abnormal anatomy</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2482-5-4-3</ID>
<CLASS>DRCT</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Necrotic gangrenous intrathoracic appendix in a marfanoid adult patient: a case report CT scan of thorax and abdomen demonstrating the abnormal anatomy</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2482-6-9-5</ID>
<CLASS>DRCT</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Splenic peliosis with spontaneous splenic rupture: report of two cases Case 2. Areas of contrast enhancement are seen more inferiorly in the spleen on CECT. These lie adjacent to a hypodense cyst-like lesion and further lacerations. The splenic capsule is disrupted anteriorly.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2482-7-6-1</ID>
<CLASS>DRCT</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Mirizzi syndrome type IV associated with cholecystocolic fistula: a very rare condition- report of a case Spiral CT with evidence of pneumobilia and suspicion of cholecystocolic fistula.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1477-7819-6-64-1</ID>
<CLASS>DRPE</CLASS>
<CAPTION>FDG PET-CT demonstration of metastatic neuroendocrine tumor of prostate Maximum intensity projection (MIP) of the whole body FDG PET-CT imaging. There is intense uptake in the prostate tumor with invasion and infiltration to the bladder wall. Multiple FDG-avid metastatic lesions are noted in the liver, Lungs and lymph nodes of the mediastinum and retroperitoneum.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1477-7819-9-70-2</ID>
<CLASS>DRPE</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Hepatic actinomycosis mimicking an isolated tumor recurrence PET scan showed abnormal robust focus of metabolic activity in inferior lateral aspect of right hepatic lobe concerning for metastatic disease (arrow) .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1746-160X-4-7-4</ID>
<CLASS>DRPE</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Distant metastases of a squamous cell carcinoma of the tongue in peripheral skeletal muscles and adjacent soft tissues Imaging by fluorine 18-fluoro-2-deoxy-glucose-positron emission tomography (18F-FDG-PET) anterior-posterior view.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1746-160X-4-7-5</ID>
<CLASS>DRPE</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Distant metastases of a squamous cell carcinoma of the tongue in peripheral skeletal muscles and adjacent soft tissues Imaging by fluorine 18-fluoro-2-deoxy-glucose-positron emission tomography (18F-FDG-PET) lateral view.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1748-717X-6-94-1</ID>
<CLASS>DRPE</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Successful radiopeptide targeting of metastatic anaplastic meningioma: Case report Maximal intensity projection visualisation of PET/CT demonstrating the intracranial meningioma and its pulmonary metastases .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1752-1947-1-148-1</ID>
<CLASS>DRPE</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Tissue is the issue-sarcoidosis following ABVD chemotherapy for Hodgkin's lymphoma: a case report PET/CT scan showing extensive areas of abnormal hypermetabolism in the mediastinum, subcarinal, left hilum, porta hepatis, celiac, retrocrural and superior mesenteric artery nodal areas. In addition, there is increased uptake in the spleen and liver.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1752-1947-1-148-3</ID>
<CLASS>DRPE</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Tissue is the issue-sarcoidosis following ABVD chemotherapy for Hodgkin's lymphoma: a case report PET/CT showing extensive hypermetabolic mediastinal adenopathy.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1752-1947-1-50-1</ID>
<CLASS>DRPE</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Primary malignant melanoma of the oesophagus: a case report FDG PET CT.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1752-1947-2-252-1</ID>
<CLASS>DRPE</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Cervical lymphadenopathy  –  an unusual presentation of carcinoma of the cervix: a case report Coronal PET image of FDG uptake in the head and neck.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1752-1947-2-252-2</ID>
<CLASS>DRPE</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Cervical lymphadenopathy  –  an unusual presentation of carcinoma of the cervix: a case report Coronal PET image of FDG uptake and excretion in the chest, abdomen and pelvis .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1752-1947-4-323-2</ID>
<CLASS>DRPE</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Successful application of technetium-99m-labeled octreotide acetate scintigraphy in the detection of ectopic adrenocorticotropin-producing bronchial carcinoid lung tumor: a case report Technetium-99m-labeled octreotide acetate scintigraphy in spot abdominal view . This was performed 3 hours after injection of 15mCi technetium-99m-labeled octreotide acetate. There is a focal uptake in the lower lobe of our patient's right lung, just above his diaphragm, highly suggestive of an adrenocorticotropic hormone (ACTH)-producing bronchial tumor.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1752-1947-5-342-1</ID>
<CLASS>DRPE</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Intramedullary spinal cord metastasis from colonic carcinoma presenting as Brown-S é quard syndrome: a case report FDG PET-CT maximum intensity projection image showing three FDG-avid pulmonary nodules .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1756-9966-27-52-2</ID>
<CLASS>DRPE</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Positron Emission Tomography (PET) radiotracers in oncology  –  utility of 18F-Fluoro-deoxy-glucose (FDG)-PET in the management of patients with non-small-cell lung cancer (NSCLC) Normal PET imaging.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1757-1626-0002-0000008420-001</ID>
<CLASS>DRPE</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Appendicular mass imitating a malignant cecal tumor on f18-FDG PET/CT study: a case report Right lower quadrant mass and urinary bladder activity in coronal section.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1757-1626-0002-0000008420-003</ID>
<CLASS>DRPE</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Appendicular mass imitating a malignant cecal tumor on f18-FDG PET/CT study: a case report Right lower quadrant mass in axial PET scan.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1757-1626-1-116-2</ID>
<CLASS>DRPE</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Mediastinal plasmacytoma with multiple myeloma presenting as a diagnostic dilemma PET scan showing hypermetabolic activity in azygoesophageal recess and right 8 th  rib.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2261-9-18-10</ID>
<CLASS>DRUS</CLASS>
<CAPTION>A systematic approach to performing a comprehensive transesophageal echocardiogram. A call to order Imaging plane 135 ° . The right upper pulmonary vein (RUPV) and superior vena cava (SVC) are demonstrated.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2261-9-18-16</ID>
<CLASS>DRUS</CLASS>
<CAPTION>A systematic approach to performing a comprehensive transesophageal echocardiogram. A call to order Imaging plane 90 ° , The two-chamber view demonstrating the anterior and inferior walls of the left ventricle (LV) .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2261-9-18-21</ID>
<CLASS>DRUS</CLASS>
<CAPTION>A systematic approach to performing a comprehensive transesophageal echocardiogram. A call to order Imaging plane 0 °  immediately before passing through the gastroesophageal junction, The RA, RV, TV and coronary sinus (CS) are demonstrated .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2261-9-18-24</ID>
<CLASS>DRUS</CLASS>
<CAPTION>A systematic approach to performing a comprehensive transesophageal echocardiogram. A call to order Imaging plane 120 ° , The transgastric view of the LV and the aortic valve (AoV) .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-230X-11-78-6</ID>
<CLASS>DRUS</CLASS>
<CAPTION>The comparison of grey-scale ultrasonic and clinical features of hepatoblastoma and hepatocellular carcinoma in children: a retrospective study for ten years HCC in the right lobe of the liver in a 10-year-old boy with hepatic cirrhosis after the HBV infection . A diffusely-distributed heterogeneous mass (arrow) with no septa or liquefaction was revealed at a setting of cirrhosis.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2334-7-12-1</ID>
<CLASS>DRUS</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Purulent pericarditis due to co-infection with  Streptococcus pneumoniae  and  Mycobacterium tuberculosis  in a patient with features of advanced HIV infection Echocardiogram showing apical collection of fluid in the pericardial space (white arrow).</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2342-8-5-3</ID>
<CLASS>DRUS</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Abdominal ultrasonography in HIV/AIDS patients in southwestern Nigeria Transverse sonogram showing extensive periportal adenopathy in a HIV+ patient with non-Hodgkin lymphoma.  AO-aorta, H-hepatic artery, SP-splenic artery, LN-lymph node.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1472-6874-6-6-4</ID>
<CLASS>DRUS</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Female genital mutilation of a karyotypic male presenting as a female with delayed puberty Ultra sound showing a mass in the prostate's position.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1475-2840-7-12-2</ID>
<CLASS>DRUS</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Treatment with pioglitazone induced significant, reversible mitral regurgitation Display of end-systolic image from apical 4-chamber view after six month of treatment with pioglitazone.  The white, thicker, arrow indicates the newly developed moderate mitral regurgitation.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1476-7120-1-16-29</ID>
<CLASS>DRUS</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Imaging of all three coronary arteries by transthoracic echocardiography. an illustrated guide Proximal part of righ coronary artery in color Doppler, parasternal short axis view.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1476-7120-1-16-31</ID>
<CLASS>DRUS</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Imaging of all three coronary arteries by transthoracic echocardiography. an illustrated guide Proximal parts of the RCA (PROX RCA) in B  –  mode; modified parasternal long axis view</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1476-7120-1-16-33</ID>
<CLASS>DRUS</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Imaging of all three coronary arteries by transthoracic echocardiography. an illustrated guide Duplex examination of proximal part of the right coronary artery (RCA) in modified apical 5-chamber view.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1476-7120-1-16-42</ID>
<CLASS>DRUS</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Imaging of all three coronary arteries by transthoracic echocardiography. an illustrated guide A bedside echocardiographic examination performed in a female patient 2 days after an acute anterior wall myocardial infarction. Parasternal short axis view at the level of papillary muscles. 2 spots of strong color signal were noted within the anterior wall; ... See movie 9 [see  Additional file 9 ]</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1476-7120-1-16-48</ID>
<CLASS>DRUS</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Imaging of all three coronary arteries by transthoracic echocardiography. an illustrated guide Doppler artifact at the anterior wall of the left ventricle. Color Doppler examination in the region of anterior interventricular groove, modified parasternal long axis view. Local, strong, linear signal mimicking high velocity flow is seen, which may easily be confused with tight middle LAD stenosis See movie 11 [see  Additional file 11 ]</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1476-7120-2-7-6</ID>
<CLASS>DRUS</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Color Doppler imaging of cervicocephalic fibromuscular dysplasia High-grade stenosis of the ICA caused by FMD in a 52-year-old woman sufferning from recurrent transient ischemic attacks. CDI shows the string-of-beads pattern distally to a longer section of normal vessel.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1476-7120-2-7-9</ID>
<CLASS>DRUS</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Color Doppler imaging of cervicocephalic fibromuscular dysplasia The same case as in fig. 6: Findings after endovascular treatment (stenting).</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1476-7120-3-14-1</ID>
<CLASS>DRUS</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Left ventricular apical thrombus after systemic thrombolysis with recombinant tissue plasminogen activator in a patient with acute ischemic stroke Cardiac duplex ultrasound image (4-chamber view), obtained 2 days after thrombolysis showing the thrombus attached to left ventricular apex (arrow).</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1476-7120-3-35-2</ID>
<CLASS>DRUS</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Coronary artery to left ventricle fistula Similar parasternal image showing the predominantly diastolic color flow image component. (RV = right ventricle, LV = left ventricle, LA = left atria).</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1476-7120-4-6-3</ID>
<CLASS>DRUS</CLASS>
<CAPTION>A case of absent right and persistent left superior vena cava Injection of agitated saline into both left and right antecubital vein results in filling of coronary sinus first followed by the filling of the right atrium (LA = left atrium, LV = left ventricle, CS = coronary sinus).</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1476-7120-5-1-2</ID>
<CLASS>DRUS</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Thickening of the pulmonary artery wall in acute intramural hematoma of the ascending aorta Short axis view at the level of the great vessels showing circumferential wall thickening of the pulmonary artery (arrow).</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1476-7120-5-10-2</ID>
<CLASS>DRUS</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Doppler findings in a rare Coronary Artery Fistula Apical site of the CAF insertion into the LV (*) and the adjacent muscular ventricular septal defect shown by color Doppler.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1476-7120-5-12-2</ID>
<CLASS>DRUS</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Subaortic and midventricular obstructive hypertrophic cardiomyopathy with extreme segmental hypertrophy A three-chamber view showing a combination of 2 different flow jets, one in the mid of left ventricle and the other in the outflow tract.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1476-7120-5-26-5</ID>
<CLASS>DRUS</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Pulmonary embolism and patent foramen ovale thrombosis: the key role of TEE Transesophageal echocardiogram (TEE transverse view 70 ° ) . Bulky and serpiginous formation referring to a thrombus that is laid through the foramen ovale and which protrudes in both atria, in burden cycles overcoming the right atrium-ventricular plane.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1476-7120-5-27-8</ID>
<CLASS>DRUS</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Echocardiographic quantification of myocardial function using tissue deformation imaging, a guide to image acquisition and analysis using tissue Doppler and speckle tracking Typical speckled pattern of the myocardium on ultrasound in the septal wall . The tracking algorithm follows a unique speckle pattern during the cardiac cycle. The red square represents the starting location and the green square the location of the pattern at end systole. Note the change in distance between the speckles due to deformation (longitudinal shortening and radial thickening of the square). RV = right ventricle; LV = left ventricle; RA = right atrium.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1476-7120-5-7-1</ID>
<CLASS>DRUS</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Two-dimensional tracking and TDI are consistent methods for evaluating myocardial longitudinal peak strain in left and right ventricle basal segments in athletes Image of "feature tracking" calculation of systolic longitudinal strain in left ventricle at rest.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1476-7120-5-9-4</ID>
<CLASS>DRUS</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Interference of breast implants with echocardiographic image acquisition and interpretation The arrow shows a large shadow and a bright ring obscuring the subcostal acoustic window.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1476-7120-6-33-4</ID>
<CLASS>DRUS</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Understanding atrioventricular septal defect: Anatomoechocardiographic correlation Two-dimensional transesophageal echocardiogram at 0 °  with color Doppler shows the shunt above the valve plane. Note the interatrial septum (asterisk). Abbreviations as before.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1476-7120-7-42-4</ID>
<CLASS>DRUS</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Respiratory maneuvers in echocardiography: a review of clinical applications Patient with dilative cardiomyopathy: M-mode at the inferior vena cava (IVC) level from subcostal view, during respiratory phases . There is no inspiratory variation of the IVC diameter, indicating increased right atrial pressure.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1476-7120-8-39-4</ID>
<CLASS>DRUS</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Standardized ultrasound evaluation of carotid stenosis for clinical trials: University of Washington Ultrasound Reading Center End Acceleration Velocity Followed by Deceleration Turbulence . Cursor 1 was placed by the examiner at the traditional location for peak systolic velocity. The Green line was added by the UWURC Reader at the End Acceleration Velocity; the red annotation was added by the UWURC Reviewer. The Doppler Angle is 47 degrees</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1476-7120-8-7-4</ID>
<CLASS>DRUS</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Echocardiography in patients with hypertrophic cardiomyopathy: usefulness of old and new techniques in the diagnosis and pathophysiological assessment Patient with left ventricular non compaction . This patient was sottoposed to echocardiography in the contest of family screening for apical hypertrophic cardiomyopathy.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1476-7120-9-26-3</ID>
<CLASS>DRUS</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Methodological approach for the assessment of ultrasound reproducibility of cardiac structure and function: a proposal of the study group of Echocardiography of the Italian Society of Cardiology (Ultra Cardia SIC) Part I Aortic root and proximal ascending aorta in parasternal long-axis view by 2-D echocardiography . By parasternal approach, a long-axis view was modified in order to maximize the imaging of the aortic valve, the sinuses of Valsalva, the sino-tubular junction and the proximal ascending aorta at end-diastole. The probe was thus swept in order to make the whole aortic root as perpendicular as possible to the ultrasound beam. Gain settings, compensation and dynamic ranges were adjusted to optimize aortic wall definition.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1477-7819-5-141-1</ID>
<CLASS>DRUS</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Laparoscopic cholecystectomy for melanoma metastatic to the gallbladder: is it an adequate surgical procedure? Report of a case and review of the literature Ultrasound evidence of metastatic melanoma of the gallbladder.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2342-6-3-4</ID>
<CLASS>DRXR</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Percutaneous subclavian artery stent-graft placement following failed ultrasound guided subclavian venous access Subclavian artery angiography in RAO 25 degree obliquity. The Wallgraft has been successfully deployed. The right internal mammary artery and the right vertebral artery are occluded. The right common carotid artery is patent and normal in appearance.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2431-5-39-1</ID>
<CLASS>DRXR</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Massive lung collapse with partial resolution after several years: a case report Chest X-ray shows persisting total atelectasis of the right lung. Note the marked loss of volume on the right, pronounced shift of the mediastinum to the right, and compensatory overexpansion of the left lung.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2458-7-260-3</ID>
<CLASS>DRXR</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Erosive Arthropathy in systemic sclerosis X-ray of hands showing a joint space narrowing in the proximal inter phalangeal joint similar to erosive osteoarthritis.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2474-11-8-1</ID>
<CLASS>DRXR</CLASS>
<CAPTION>A randomised controlled trial of total hip arthroplasty versus resurfacing arthroplasty in the treatment of young patients with arthritis of the hip joint X-ray showing a Total Hip Arthroplasty (THA) and a Resurfacing Arthroplasty (RSA) .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2474-3-5-2</ID>
<CLASS>DRXR</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Ligamentous rupture of the ACL associated with dislocated fracture of the proximal tibial physis in a 12-year-old boy The initial radiograph (anterio-posterior view) reveals an opened physeal plate (medial) and a small metaphyseal fracture.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2474-3-5-5</ID>
<CLASS>DRXR</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Ligamentous rupture of the ACL associated with dislocated fracture of the proximal tibial physis in a 12-year-old boy Four weeks after the accident: the radiograph shows good alignment (lateral view).</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2474-6-13-3</ID>
<CLASS>DRXR</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Complex Pediatric Elbow Injury: An Uncommon Case Postoperative anteroposterior radiograph of the elbow revealing internal fixation of the lateral condyle fracture with the help of 2 K-wires. The elbow dislocation was reduced first by closed technique.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2474-9-66-3</ID>
<CLASS>DRXR</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Percutaneous acetabuloplasty for metastatic acetabular lesions Preoperative plain radiographs showing wide acetabular osteolysis.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2482-3-12-1</ID>
<CLASS>DRXR</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Clasp knife in the gut: a case report X-ray abdomen (lateral view) showing the blade of a knife in the abdomen.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1476-7120-1-2-1</ID>
<CLASS>DRXR</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Patent ductus arteriosus endarteritis in a 40-year old woman, diagnosed with Transesophageal Echocardiography. A case report and a brief review of the literature Chest X-ray showing a consolidation at the base of the right lung (arrow).</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1477-5751-5-12-3</ID>
<CLASS>DRXR</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Radiographic 2D:4D index in females: no relation to anthropometric, behavioural, nutritional, health-related, occupational or fertility variables Osteoarthritis makes joint spaces narrow and thus biases finger length measurements.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1477-7800-5-11-4</ID>
<CLASS>DRXR</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Exophytic growth of a neglected giant subcutaneous Leiomyosarcoma of the lower extremity. A case report Post-operative Anteroposterior X-Ray view of the proximal tibia. Bone resection was decided for the achievement of wide and tumor-free surgical margins.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1477-7819-5-123-1</ID>
<CLASS>DRXR</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Extramedullary plasmacytoma (EMP): Report of a case manifested as a mediastinal mass and multiple pulmonary nodules and review of literature The chest X-ray revealed multiple pulmonary nodular lesions.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1746-1340-15-18-1</ID>
<CLASS>DRXR</CLASS>
<CAPTION>A case report of bilateral synovial chondromatosis of the ankle Lateral right ankle radiograph with evidence of calcified loose bodies (arrow) posterior to the talotibial joint. Small loose bodies are also seen anteriorly to the joint (arrow head).</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1748-7161-3-11-1</ID>
<CLASS>DRXR</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Differential wedging of vertebral body and intervertebral disc in thoracic and lumbar spine in adolescent idiopathic scoliosis  –  A cross sectional study in 150 patients Roentgen graphic assessment was performed with whole spine standing radiogram including pelvis in all patients.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1749-7922-2-27-1</ID>
<CLASS>DRXR</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Laparoscopic repair of strangulated Morgagni hernia Chest x-ray on admission showing an unusual air fluid level in the lower chest.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1749-7922-5-19-6</ID>
<CLASS>DRXR</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Transverse colon volvulus in a 15 year old boy and the review of the literature Water Soluble Contrast Enema - Contrast was introduced per rectum . This was seen to flow freely to the right side of the abdomen within the bowel. No extravasation of contrast or stricture was demonstrated.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1749-799X-4-39-2</ID>
<CLASS>DRXR</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Mid-term results and factors affecting outcome of a metal-backed unicompartmental knee design: a case series Post-operative antero-posterior radiograph of the same patient shown in Figure 1 at 6 week follow-up visit .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1749-799X-5-62-1</ID>
<CLASS>DRXR</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Medial pelvic migration of the lag screw in a short gamma nail after hip fracture fixation: a case report and review of the literature Anterior-Posterior radiograph demonstrating a three part intertrochanteric hip fracture on the right side . Discontinuety of the medial contex is seen with the less trochanter fracture fragment.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1749-799X-5-79-1</ID>
<CLASS>DRXR</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Unicameral bone cyst of the lunate in an adult: case report PA radiograph of the right wrist . There was a radiolucent lesion measuring 11 mm in diameter at the center of the lunate with round margins. There was no scalloping, septae formation or cortical thinning.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1749-8090-3-32-1</ID>
<CLASS>DRXR</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Massive benign pericardial cyst presenting with simultaneous superior vena cava and middle lobe syndromes Chest X ray (PA) view showing a large mediastinal mass occupying middle and lower zones of right chest and causing compressive atelectasis of middle lobe.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2261-1-3-1</ID>
<CLASS>DSEC</CLASS>
<CAPTION>5-Fluorouracil-induced cardiotoxicity mimicking myocardial infarction: a case report ECG taken at time of chest pain</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2261-1-3-2</ID>
<CLASS>DSEC</CLASS>
<CAPTION>5-Fluorouracil-induced cardiotoxicity mimicking myocardial infarction: a case report ECG after pain resolved</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2261-10-30-3</ID>
<CLASS>DSEC</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Establishment of a canine model of cardiac memory using endocardial pacing via internal jugular vein Canine ECG during ventricular pacing .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2261-5-6-3</ID>
<CLASS>DSEC</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Acute ST-segment elevation myocardial infarction after amoxycillin-induced anaphylactic shock in a young adult with normal coronary arteries: a case report ECG recorded on hospital day 4 th .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-227X-5-10-1</ID>
<CLASS>DSEC</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Flecainide overdose  –  support using an intra-aortic balloon pump 12-lead ECG on admission.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-227X-5-10-2</ID>
<CLASS>DSEC</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Flecainide overdose  –  support using an intra-aortic balloon pump 12-lead ECG after thrombolysis.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-227X-5-10-3</ID>
<CLASS>DSEC</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Flecainide overdose  –  support using an intra-aortic balloon pump 12-lead ECG after treatment.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-227X-5-5-1</ID>
<CLASS>DSEC</CLASS>
<CAPTION>QT interval prolongation after sertraline overdose: a case report ECGs of the patient. ECG of the patient upon admission (upper panel) shows a normal sinus rhythm with a QT interval in lead V2 of 370 ms (QT c  420 ms). There were negative T-waves in leads V1 – V3. A second ECG was obtained one day after admission (lower panel) shows a markedly prolonged QT interval of 520 ms in V2 (QT c  525 ms).</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2350-9-24-2</ID>
<CLASS>DSEC</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Identification of a novel  KCNQ1  mutation associated with both Jervell and Lange-Nielsen and Romano-Ward forms of long QT syndrome in a Chinese family Representative electrocardiograms (ECG) from members of the Chinese family with LQTS. Top, ECG from a normal family member (I-1); Middle, ECG from a heterozygous mutation carrier; Bottom, ECG from a homozygous mutation carrier.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1475-925X-1-5-3</ID>
<CLASS>DSEC</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Cardiac arrhythmia classification using autoregressive modeling A patient ECG and simulated ECG having NSR</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1475-925X-1-5-4</ID>
<CLASS>DSEC</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Cardiac arrhythmia classification using autoregressive modeling A patient ECG and simulated ECG with APC</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1475-925X-1-5-5</ID>
<CLASS>DSEC</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Cardiac arrhythmia classification using autoregressive modeling A patient ECG and simulated ECG with PVC</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1475-925X-1-5-6</ID>
<CLASS>DSEC</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Cardiac arrhythmia classification using autoregressive modeling A patient ECG and simulated ECG with SVT</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1475-925X-1-5-7</ID>
<CLASS>DSEC</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Cardiac arrhythmia classification using autoregressive modeling A patient ECG and simulated ECG with VT</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1475-925X-1-5-8</ID>
<CLASS>DSEC</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Cardiac arrhythmia classification using autoregressive modeling A patient ECG and simulated ECG with VF</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1475-925X-4-6-1</ID>
<CLASS>DSEC</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Life-threatening ventricular arrhythmia recognition by nonlinear descriptor Typical life-threatening ECG waveform of NSR</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1475-925X-4-6-2</ID>
<CLASS>DSEC</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Life-threatening ventricular arrhythmia recognition by nonlinear descriptor Typical life-threatening ECG waveform of VT</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1475-925X-4-6-3</ID>
<CLASS>DSEC</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Life-threatening ventricular arrhythmia recognition by nonlinear descriptor Typical life-threatening ECG waveform of VF</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1476-7120-5-39-1</ID>
<CLASS>DSEC</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Clinical significance of intraventricular gradient during effort in an adolescent karate player Normal ECG.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1477-9560-7-6-2</ID>
<CLASS>DSEC</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Clopidogrel resistance "Live"  –  the risk of stent thrombosis should be evaluated before procedures ECG at the second hospital admission .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1749-8090-4-29-1</ID>
<CLASS>DSEC</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Unstable angina early after aortic valve replacement surgery in a female patient with normal coronary arteries preoperatively  –  a case report Preopoerative ECG: Regular sinus rhythm .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1752-1947-2-100-1</ID>
<CLASS>DSEC</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Pneumopericardium should be considered with electrocardiogram changes after blunt chest trauma: a case report ECG performed on admission.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1752-1947-5-524-4</ID>
<CLASS>DSEC</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Acute left ventricular dysfunction secondary to right ventricular septal pacing in a woman with initial preserved contractility: a case report Twelve lead ECG after CRT .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1757-1626-0002-0000008176-001</ID>
<CLASS>DSEC</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Malignancy with unknown primary presenting as acute cardiac tamponade: a case report ECG on admission. The admission ECG demonstrating slightly reduced QRS complexes.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1757-1626-0002-0000008278-001</ID>
<CLASS>DSEC</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Electrocardiographic changes in hiatal hernia: a case report Electrocardiogram (ECG) showing T wave inversion in precordial leads V1-V3.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1757-1626-1-309-1</ID>
<CLASS>DSEC</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Atypical presentation of "takotsubo cardiomyopathy" without ST segment elevation: a case report Initial electrocardiography (ECG) during attack.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1757-1626-1-51-3</ID>
<CLASS>DSEC</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Atrial septal aneurysm associated with additional cardiovascular comorbidities in two middle age female patients with ECG signs of right bundle branch block: two case reports ECG of the first patient . Precordial ECG leads showing signs of RBBB.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1757-1626-2-73-1</ID>
<CLASS>DSEC</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Brugada ECG pattern precipitated by acute pneumonia: a case report Brugada ECG pattern .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1757-7241-18-19-1</ID>
<CLASS>DSEC</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Favourable outcome after 26 minutes of "Compression only" resuscitation: a case report First recorded ECG .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2334-6-169-1</ID>
<CLASS>DSEE</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Novel mutation of the  PRNP  gene of a clinical CJD case Electroencephalogram of the suspected CJD patient showing typical periodic bursts of triphasic sharp waves.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2377-5-14-1</ID>
<CLASS>DSEE</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Observations on comatose survivors of cardiopulmonary resuscitation with generalized myoclonus Three examples of a burst-suppression-EEG of 3 comatose survivors with generalized myoclonus within 24 hours after cardiopulmonary resuscitation.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2377-5-14-2</ID>
<CLASS>DSEE</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Observations on comatose survivors of cardiopulmonary resuscitation with generalized myoclonus Burst-suppression-EEG (upper recording) with periods of continuous epileptiform discharges (lower recording) in a comatose survivors of cardiopulmonary resuscitation with generalized myoclonus.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2377-5-14-4</ID>
<CLASS>DSEE</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Observations on comatose survivors of cardiopulmonary resuscitation with generalized myoclonus Examples of alpha-coma-EEGs on the 2 nd  day after cardiopulmonary resuscitation in 2 comatose survivors with burst-suppression EEG on the preceding day.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2377-5-14-5</ID>
<CLASS>DSEE</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Observations on comatose survivors of cardiopulmonary resuscitation with generalized myoclonus Examples of continuous epileptiform discharges on the 2 nd  day after cardiopulmonary resuscitation in 2 comatose survivors with burst-suppression EEG on the preceding day.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2377-5-14-6</ID>
<CLASS>DSEE</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Observations on comatose survivors of cardiopulmonary resuscitation with generalized myoclonus EEG-sequence of a comatose survivors of cardiopulmonary resuscitation with a burst-suppression-EEG on the 1 st  day, which was followed by an alpha-coma-EEG on the 2 nd  and an isolelectric recording on the 4 th  day.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2377-5-14-7</ID>
<CLASS>DSEE</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Observations on comatose survivors of cardiopulmonary resuscitation with generalized myoclonus "Transitional"-EEG-pattern between burst-suppression-EEG and continuous epileptiform discharges (upper recording) or between alpha-and theta-coma EEG (lower recording).</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1751-0759-3-2-1</ID>
<CLASS>DSEE</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Biopsychosocial approaches to a patient with vomiting of 10 years' duration  –  a case of temporal lobe epilepsy High amplitude slow waves . EEG showed high amplitude, 5 – 6 Hz and slow waves during the vomiting-free periods.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1751-0759-3-2-2</ID>
<CLASS>DSEE</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Biopsychosocial approaches to a patient with vomiting of 10 years' duration  –  a case of temporal lobe epilepsy High amplitude slow waves correlated with vomiting . EEG with light symptoms. The increase in irregular waves correlated with vomiting. EEGs during severe vomiting could not be recorded properly.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1751-0759-3-2-5</ID>
<CLASS>DSEE</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Biopsychosocial approaches to a patient with vomiting of 10 years' duration  –  a case of temporal lobe epilepsy EEG with administration of clonazepam . Slow waves decreased and changed to regular background waves four months after administration of clonazepam 1 mg.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1751-0759-3-2-7</ID>
<CLASS>DSEE</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Biopsychosocial approaches to a patient with vomiting of 10 years' duration  –  a case of temporal lobe epilepsy EEG after treatment . EEG after implementing biopsychosocial approaches. The patient had no vomiting and had discontinued medication. Irregular waves were evident in the background, although there were no high amplitude slow waves.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1751-0759-4-9-1</ID>
<CLASS>DSEE</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Electroencephalogram abnormalities in panic disorder patients: a study of symptom characteristics and pathology EEG record of Case 11 . EEG Result: Basic activity is 12~13 Hz 20~50  μ V with regular  α  waves. 6-7 Hz  θ  wave activities appear in the posterior and central channels occasionally. Judgment of this EEG is slightly abnormal.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1751-0759-4-9-2</ID>
<CLASS>DSEE</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Electroencephalogram abnormalities in panic disorder patients: a study of symptom characteristics and pathology EEG record of Case 5 . EEG Result: Basic activity is 10-11 Hz 30~100  μ V with regular or irregular  α  waves. Sharp&  slow wave complexes appear in the right a few times. Judgment of this EEG is slightly abnormal.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1752-1947-5-264-2</ID>
<CLASS>DSEE</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Stroke with neuropsychiatric sequelae after cannabis use in a man: a case report Electroencephalographic (EEG) recording obtained within 24 hours after the patient's sixth generalized tonic-clonic seizure . The EEG tracing shows brief pseudorhythmic  θ  activity that predominated bifrontally.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1753-4631-4-2-1</ID>
<CLASS>DSEE</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Research on the relation of EEG signal chaos characteristics with high-level intelligence activity of human brain EEG signal waveform of subject 1 while relaxing .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1755-7682-1-5-3</ID>
<CLASS>DSEE</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Partial trisomy 13q22-qter associated to leukoencephalopathy and late onset generalised epilepsy EEG showed normal background activity and polyspike generalised discharges.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1755-7682-4-23-1</ID>
<CLASS>DSEE</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Periodic lateralized epileptiform discharges as manifestation of pneumococcal meningoencephalitis The EEG on day 2 showed periodic lateralized epileptiform discharges (PLEDs) every 3-4 seconds in the left frontal and temporal lobes, and theta slowing in right hemisphere .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1755-7682-4-23-2</ID>
<CLASS>DSEE</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Periodic lateralized epileptiform discharges as manifestation of pneumococcal meningoencephalitis The EEG after treatment with antibiotics reported as normal showing no PLEDs .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1757-1626-0002-0000007069-001</ID>
<CLASS>DSEE</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Nonconvulsive status epilepticus manifesting as bradyphrenia: a case report Electroencephalogram showing bilateral diffuse synchronous epileptic discharges (electrical status epilepticus).</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1757-1626-1-425-1</ID>
<CLASS>DSEE</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Atypical onset of diabetes in a teenage girl: a case report Awake EEG, no chorea-ballismus .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>cc9276-1</ID>
<CLASS>DSEE</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Prognostic value of continuous EEG monitoring during therapeutic hypothermia after cardiac arrest EEG recording performed during therapeutic hypothermia from one representative patient who had a good outcome (Cerebral Performance Category 1 at 2 months) . EEG shows a reactive EEG background activity to sound ("claps"); recording, 30 mm/sec, 10  μ V/mm.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-230X-3-28-2</ID>
<CLASS>DSEM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Anorectal motility in patients with achalasia of the esophagus: recognition of an esophago-rectal syndrome EMG of the external anal sphincter showing normal activity a- at rest. b- upon contraction.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-230X-3-28-3</ID>
<CLASS>DSEM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Anorectal motility in patients with achalasia of the esophagus: recognition of an esophago-rectal syndrome EMG of the levator ani muscle showing diminished activity. a- at rest. b- upon contraction.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2318-8-33-3</ID>
<CLASS>DSEM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>The feasibility of measuring the activation of the trunk muscles in healthy older adults during trunk stability exercises Raw EMG data . Examples of the raw EMG signals from the lower rectus abdominus [LRA], and external oblique [EO3]  during level 3 of the exercise progression. This provides an indication of the quality of the data.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2474-11-46-2</ID>
<CLASS>DSEM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Load and speed effects on the cervical flexion relaxation phenomenon Typical subject EMG (grey) and cervical flexion angle (black) during a slow-speed-without-load trial .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2474-9-10-1</ID>
<CLASS>DSEM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Changes in the flexion relaxation response induced by lumbar muscle fatigue Scaled EMG raw signal and total trunk angle from a subject performing a FRP task in a no load, no fatigue condition.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2490-7-5-2</ID>
<CLASS>DSEM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Is abdominal wall contraction important for normal voiding in the female rat? Time-expansion of voiding-associated EMG changes . Time-expanded tracings demonstrating changes in rectus abdominis and perineal EMG activity accompanying voiding. Top tracing is voided volume, middle tracing is rectus abdominis EMG, and bottom tracing is perineal EMG tracing. Pulse width of perineal EMG tracing indicated by vertical lines, interval is 0.2 second.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2490-8-4-3</ID>
<CLASS>DSEM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Study of the response of the penile corporal tissue and cavernosus muscles to micturition The EMG activity of (a) bulbocavernosus muscle at rest, (b) ischiocavernosus muscle at rest, (c) bulbocavernosus muscle during micturition, and (d) ischiocavernosus muscle during micturition .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1476-5918-5-7-1</ID>
<CLASS>DSEM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Shoulder muscle EMG activity during push up variations on and off a Swiss ball EMG linear envelopes during a push ups with the hands on an exercise bench and a Swiss ball. EMG activity is non-normalized and is therefore in arbitrary EMG units. A bias was added to the activity of the pectoralis major, rectus abdominis and external oblique for ease of viewing to prevent overlap of the muscle's linear envelopes. Three pushups occurred over the course of 30 seconds.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1476-5918-5-7-3</ID>
<CLASS>DSEM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Shoulder muscle EMG activity during push up variations on and off a Swiss ball Raw EMG for Rectus Abdominis and External Oblique muscles during three push ups with the hands on or off a Swiss ball. EO = External Oblique, RA = Rectus Abdominis.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1746-160X-3-26-3</ID>
<CLASS>DSEM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Standardization of surface electromyography utilized to evaluate patients with dysphagia Stages of the normal swallow (reflex part). Horizontal mark 3  –  water intake, 3.5 – 4  –  final oral stage, 4 – 4.5  –  pharyngeal stage, 4.5 – 5.5  –  initial esophageal stage. Upper peak  –  submental location, middle peak  –  masseter location, lower peak  –  infrahyoid muscles location. Total electric activity duration after water intake: 2.5 sec.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1749-7221-3-18-1</ID>
<CLASS>DSEM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Spinal myoclonus following a peripheral nerve injury: a case report EMG recordings with surface electrodes . EMG channesl: 1-M. Orbicularis oris 2-M. Trapezius 3-M. Rhomboideus 4-M. Pectoralis 5-M. Biceps Brachii 6-M,. Triceps 7-Forearm flexor muscles 8-Forearm extansor muscles.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1749-8546-3-17-3</ID>
<CLASS>DSEM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>The immediate effects of local and adjacent acupuncture on the tibialis anterior muscle: a human study Electromyography (EMG) of a single subject in the local point ST36 group . A = EMG acupuncture. B = EMG after acupuncture. In the x axis the duration is 5 seconds. In the y axis the amplitude scale is 308  μ V in A and 102  μ V in B.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1749-8546-3-17-4</ID>
<CLASS>DSEM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>The immediate effects of local and adjacent acupuncture on the tibialis anterior muscle: a human study Electromyography (EMG) of a single subject in the adjacent point SP9 group . A = EMG before acupuncture. B = EMG after acupuncture. In the x axis the duration is 5 seconds. In the y axis the amplitude scale is 33  μ V in A and 25  μ V in B.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1757-1626-1-167-1</ID>
<CLASS>DSEM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>The effect of facial muscle contractions on the cerebral state index in an ICU patient: A case report CSI curve of the patient . CSI: cerebral state index, BS: burst suppression, EMG: electromyogram. 1: first injection of atracurium (25 mg), 2: second injection of atracurium(15 mg). As appeared in the figure, CSI changes follow the EMG changes. BS increases when EMG decreases.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>cc5139-1</ID>
<CLASS>DSEM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Neuromuscular deterioration in the early stage of sepsis in rats A sample of compound muscle action potential recorded before laparotomy in the sham group. EMG, electromyelograph.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>cc5139-2</ID>
<CLASS>DSEM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Neuromuscular deterioration in the early stage of sepsis in rats A sample of compound muscle action potential recorded 24 hours after laparotomy in the sham group. EMG, electromyelograph.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>cc5139-3</ID>
<CLASS>DSEM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Neuromuscular deterioration in the early stage of sepsis in rats A sample of compound muscle action potential recorded before cecal ligation and puncture in the sepsis group. EMG, electromyelograph.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>cc5139-4</ID>
<CLASS>DSEM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Neuromuscular deterioration in the early stage of sepsis in rats A sample of compound muscle action potential sample recorded 24 hours after cecal ligation and puncture in the sepsis group. EMG, electromyelograph.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1742-4755-1-4-3</ID>
<CLASS>DVDM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Idiopathic isolated clitoromegaly: A report of two cases Traction of the clitoris per-operatively.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1746-160X-4-2-12</ID>
<CLASS>DVDM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Cutaneous lesions of the external ear Cylindroma. Numerous pink, red, and partially bluish, firm nodules, affecting the upper parts of the ear and spreading to the left cheek. The distribution and arrangement of tumor masses resemble a bunch of grapes.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1746-160X-4-2-3</ID>
<CLASS>DVDM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Cutaneous lesions of the external ear Basalioma. Erythematous papule with indicated pearly border. Remark the central ulceration of the retroauricular located lesion.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1746-160X-4-2-6</ID>
<CLASS>DVDM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Cutaneous lesions of the external ear Superficial spreading melanoma. Dark and flat macule with variegated colors. Its borders are irregular, with indentations and notches.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1746-160X-4-2-7</ID>
<CLASS>DVDM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Cutaneous lesions of the external ear Lentigo maligna melanoma. Irregular pigmented and bordered, brown to black macule with visible bright to reddish regression zone.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1746-160X-6-7-10</ID>
<CLASS>DVDM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Cutaneous lesions of the nose Facial eosinophilic granuloma . Red-brown nodule on the nose. Clearly visible follicular structures ("peau d'orange").</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1746-160X-6-7-16</ID>
<CLASS>DVDM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Cutaneous lesions of the nose Pigmented BCC . Dark nodule (resulting from melanin deposition) at the alar of the nose. Small ulceration at the center.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1746-160X-6-7-17</ID>
<CLASS>DVDM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Cutaneous lesions of the nose Scar-like morphea-like BCC . Sclerotic, partially reddish plaque. Crusting in the center.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1746-160X-6-7-5</ID>
<CLASS>DVDM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Cutaneous lesions of the nose Rhinophyma . Large exophytic, pink, lobulated mass over the nose with superficial vascular dilation. The lesion is spreading to the cheeks; however, it can also be limited to the nose.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1746-160X-6-7-7</ID>
<CLASS>DVDM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Cutaneous lesions of the nose Nevus araneus (spider nevus) . In the center of the red lesion a small (1 mm) red papule is visible, surrounded by several distinct radiating vessels. Pressure on the lesion causes it to disappear. Blanching is replaced by rapid refill from the central arteriole when pressure is released.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1748-717X-5-38-1</ID>
<CLASS>DVDM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Lack of Cetuximab induced skin toxicity in a previously irradiated field: case report and review of the literature Left face: Showing lack of skin rash in the previously irradiated area .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1748-717X-5-38-2</ID>
<CLASS>DVDM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Lack of Cetuximab induced skin toxicity in a previously irradiated field: case report and review of the literature Right Face: Previous unirradiated side showing typical Cetuximab induced skin rash .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1749-7221-2-12-2</ID>
<CLASS>DVDM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Platysma motor branch transfer in brachial plexus repair: report of the first case Schematic representation of the surgical procedure to connect the (Pb) platysma motor branch to the (MP) medial pectoral nerve. A (SN) sural nerve graft was used to connect donor and recipient nerves.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1749-8090-6-119-1</ID>
<CLASS>DVDM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Surgical treatment of giant plexiform neurofibroma associated with pectus excavatum Preoperative photograph of the chest wall .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1750-1172-4-19-4</ID>
<CLASS>DVDM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Erythropoietic protoporphyria Chronic skin lesions of EPP .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1752-1947-0003-0000007023-6</ID>
<CLASS>DVDM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Therapeutic effect of hyperbaric oxygen in psoriasis vulgaris: two case reports and a review of the literature Patient 2 after treatment with hyperbaric oxygen (Side View Torso) .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1752-1947-0003-0000007071-3</ID>
<CLASS>DVDM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Liposarcoma of the forearm in a man with type 1 neurofibromatosis: a case report Generalized neurofibromatosis . Note the scar on the left forearm after resection of the liposarcoma.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1752-1947-2-282-1</ID>
<CLASS>DVDM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Disseminated cutaneous Herpes Simplex Virus-1 in a woman with rheumatoid arthritis receiving Infliximab: A case report Scaly pustular lesions on soles of feet typical of pustular psoriasis .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1752-1947-4-106-2</ID>
<CLASS>DVDM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Renal cancer associated with recurrent spontaneous pneumothorax in Birt-Hogg-Dub é  syndrome: a case report and review of the literature Multiple pale, dome-shaped macules over our patient's face . Histologically these were found to be fibrofolliculomas, the characteristic skin lesion of Birt-Hogg-Dub é  syndrome.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1754-9493-2-12-4</ID>
<CLASS>DVDM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Skin avulsion injury during endotracheal tube extubation  –  case report of an unusual complication Full take of the skin graft following replacement as a graft (1 week after surgery).</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1755-7682-2-22-2</ID>
<CLASS>DVDM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>A 44 year-old lady with chronic renal disease and intractable ulcers: a case report Extensive involvement of the thighs and lower abdomen .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1756-3305-1-40-6</ID>
<CLASS>DVDM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Oh my aching gut: irritable bowel syndrome,  Blastocystis , and asymptomatic infection Rash from 39-year old US male diagnosed with chronic blastocystosis acquired domestically [ 60 ]. Skin rash in  Blastocystis  infection has been described as recurrent [ 65 ] and intensely pruritic [ 67 ]. Diagnosis of blastocystosis was by exclusion: eleven ova and parasite exams (trichrome staining) performed at clinical laboratories from 2003 – 2006 were negative except for findings of  Blastocystis . Colonoscopy, endoscopy, and gluten challenge test were negative. The infection was unresponsive to metronidazole, nitazoxanide, and TMP/SMX. The isolate was genotyped as  Blastocystis  sp. subtype 3 in a 2007 study [ 49 ].</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1757-1146-1-11-1</ID>
<CLASS>DVDM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Acral lentiginous melanoma of the foot and ankle: A case series and review of the literature Acral lentiginous melanoma on the plantar surface.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1757-1146-2-14-1</ID>
<CLASS>DVDM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Dermoscopy as a technique for the early identification of foot melanoma Superficial spreading melanoma on the ankle .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1757-1146-2-14-2</ID>
<CLASS>DVDM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Dermoscopy as a technique for the early identification of foot melanoma Acral lentiginous melanoma .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1757-1626-0002-0000006500-002</ID>
<CLASS>DVDM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Perniosis (chilblains) masquerading as CA-MRSA: a case report Perniosis of the toes, example that could be confusing.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1757-1626-0002-0000007532-004</ID>
<CLASS>DVDM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Surgical removal of a tea spoon from the ascending colon, ten years after ingestion: a case report Follow up in 2 months.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1757-1626-1-79-1</ID>
<CLASS>DVDM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Rapidly evolving purpuric lesions to massive hemorrhagic bullae, with rapid improvement by Prednisolone: as a coetaneous manifestation of Systemic Lupus Erythematosus: a case report Fulminant pethechia/purpura on the limbs in the first day of admission.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>cde0001-0011-f02</ID>
<CLASS>DVDM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Dermoscopy of Pigmented Bowen's Disease Mimicking Early Superficial Spreading Melanoma Dermoscopy demonstrates atypical pigment network and dotted vessels. Irregular flossy streaks are also partially noted.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>cde0002-0183-f02</ID>
<CLASS>DVDM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Psoriatic Pseudobalanitis Circinata as a Post-Viral Koebner Phenomenon After 1 month, new lesions presenting as pseudo-anular circinate whitish flat papules were observed. This histology confirmed the presence of psoriasis.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>cde0002-0201-f05</ID>
<CLASS>DVDM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Sequential Acral Lentiginous Melanomas of the Foot Dermoscopy of the second lesion shows multiple components made of a parallel ridge pattern, with irregular distribution of small melanin dots and a focal hypopigmented component.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>cde0003-0235-f02</ID>
<CLASS>DVDM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Epidermolysis Bullosa Nevi: Report of a Case and Review of the Literature Dermoscopic aspect of the mole.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>DRP2009-679010.001</ID>
<CLASS>DVDM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Desmoplastic Melanoma: Report of 5 Cases Clinical appearance of desmoplastic melanoma (patient n ° 4): red plaque of 5  ×  3   cm on left leg. The diagnoses that are suspected clinically range from basal cell carcinoma to dermatofibrosarcoma protuberans or amelanotic melanoma.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>DRP2010-285392.001</ID>
<CLASS>DVDM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Dermoscopy of Cylindroma Polarized light dermoscopy.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>DRP2010-285392.002</ID>
<CLASS>DVDM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Dermoscopy of Cylindroma Contact dermoscopy.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>DRP2010-464821.006</ID>
<CLASS>DVDM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Dermoscopy Clues in Pigmented Bowen's Disease Case 1 . Closeup view of upper third of the lesion with peripheral streaks, central brown and blue-gray pigmentation with keratosis and brown globules in a linear arrangement.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>DRP2010-543091.002</ID>
<CLASS>DVDM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Dermoscopic Features of Pigmented Bowen's Disease in a Japanese Female Mimicking Malignant Melanoma Dermoscopic examination demonstrated irregular flossy streaks, irregular brown dots/globules, and blue-whitish regression structures with overlying whitish scaly areas.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>DRP2010-709371.002</ID>
<CLASS>DVDM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Ectopic Hidradenoma Papilliferum Dermoscopy findings.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>IJD-53-201-g001</ID>
<CLASS>DVDM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>UNUSUAL PRESENTATION OF GENERALIZED MACULAR AMYLOIDOSIS IN A YOUNG ADULT Hypopigmented macules over abdomen</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>IJD-53-206-g005</ID>
<CLASS>DVDM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>CUTANEOUS PANCREATIC METASTASIS: A CASE REPORT AND REVIEW OF LITERATURE One month later, after receiving the treatment, the reddish, nontender indurated plaques increased in size to cover the entire left side of the neck</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>IJD-53-217-g001</ID>
<CLASS>DVDM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>SCLEREDEMA DIABETICORUM WITH UNUSUAL PRESENTATION AND FATAL OUTCOME Corrugated skin in both thighs with erythematous induration and hyperpigmentation</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>IJD-53-221-g001</ID>
<CLASS>DVDM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>GENERALIZED LICHEN NITIDUS IN CHILDHOOD Skin-colored shiny papules on hands</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>IJD-53-221-g003</ID>
<CLASS>DVDM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>GENERALIZED LICHEN NITIDUS IN CHILDHOOD Shiny papules on abdomen</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>IJD-53-80-g001</ID>
<CLASS>DVDM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>HIV AND LUPUS ERYTHEMATOSUS: A DIAGNOSTIC DILEMMA Malar erythema with minimal involvement of nasolabial fold</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>IJD-54-132-g003</ID>
<CLASS>DVDM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>CUTANEOUS MANIFESTATIONS OF SYSTEMIC LUPUS ERYTHEMATOSUS IN A TERTIARY REFERRAL CENTER A case of DLE on the scalp with scarring alopecia</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>IJD-54-137-g001</ID>
<CLASS>DVDM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>OCCUPATIONAL ALLERGIC CONTACT DERMATITIS AMONG CONSTRUCTION WORKERS IN INDIA Discrete papular eruptions over exposed areas of forearm and arm with relative sparing trunk</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>IJD-54-137-g002</ID>
<CLASS>DVDM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>OCCUPATIONAL ALLERGIC CONTACT DERMATITIS AMONG CONSTRUCTION WORKERS IN INDIA Same patient showing presence of similar papular eruptions over proximal part of dorsum of hand with characteristic sparing of fingers</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>IJD-54-150-g002</ID>
<CLASS>DVDM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>TISSUE GRAFTS IN VITILIGO SURGERY  –  PAST, PRESENT, AND FUTURE Blisters formed after 2 hours of suction</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>IJD-54-62-g001</ID>
<CLASS>DVDM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>CHILDHOOD HERPES ZOSTER: A CLUSTERING OF TEN CASES Case 3 - Grouped vesicles on erythematous base, over left thoracic (T10, 11) dermatomes. Herbal paste has been applied overneath</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>IJD-54-72-g001</ID>
<CLASS>DVDM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>MULTIPLE CUTANEOUS LEIOMYOMAS: PAIN RELIEF WITH PULSED HYSOCINE BUTYL BROMIDE Lesions over the forehead</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>IJD-54-72-g002</ID>
<CLASS>DVDM</CLASS>
<CAPTION>MULTIPLE CUTANEOUS LEIOMYOMAS: PAIN RELIEF WITH PULSED HYSOCINE BUTYL BROMIDE Extensive lesions over the back</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-230X-10-109-1</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Duodenal carcinoma at the ligament of Treitz. A molecular and clinical perspective Endoscopic image of the small bowel neoplasm . The endoscopic image of the cancerous mass showing it's large irregular pattern and causing narrowing of the duodenum.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-230X-10-2-1</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>The clinical presentations of ectopic biliary drainage into duodenal bulbus and stomach with a thorough review of the current literature A case with ectopic bilio-pancreatic drainage into the stomach . Biliary orifice is indicated by taller arrow. The pancreatic duct orifice is shown by smaller arrow. It is clear to see small amount of bile staining the biliary orifice.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-230X-10-75-1</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Case report: acute pancreatitis caused by postcholecystectomic hemobilia initial endoscopy demonstrating blood leakage through duodenal papilla .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-230X-10-84-1</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Chemical gastritis after chronic bromazepam intake: a case report Endoscopy appearance of the gastric antrum with discoloration after bromazepam intake .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-230X-10-84-2</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Chemical gastritis after chronic bromazepam intake: a case report Discoloration of the duodenal bulb after bromazepam intake .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-230X-10-87-4</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Recurrent advanced colonic cancer occurring 11 years after initial endoscopic piecemeal resection: a case report Follow up colonoscopy in 2007 revealed a protruding subumucosal tumor (SMT) at the initial resection site (a), after indigo carmine dye (b) .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-230X-2-15-1</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Bouveret's syndrome complicated by distal gallstone ileus after laser lithotropsy using Holmium: YAG laser Large obstructing gallstone just beyond the duodenal bulb with ulcerated duodenal wall.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-230X-3-16-3</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Antral hyperplastic polyp causing intermittent gastric outlet obstruction: Case report A complete healing at the polypectomy site was observed on the follow-up endoscopy after a 12-week course of PPI therapy.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-230X-3-2-1</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Dieulafoy's lesion of duodenum: a case report DL of the duodenum.  Note the deformed duodenal bulb with small clot adherent to the mucosa in the postbulbar area. The mucosa is normal and there is no evidence of any duodenal ulcer. Lesion was missed on (first) endoscopy because it was covered with the tiny clot and the surrounding mucosa was normal.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-230X-3-2-2</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Dieulafoy's lesion of duodenum: a case report DL of the duodenum.  An actively bleeding DL in the postbulbar duodenum (same case shown in Figure  1 ). Repeat endoscopy, 24 hours later, immediately following rebleeding showed actively bleeding vessel in postbulbar duodenum. The surrounding mucosa is edematous because of adrenaline injection.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-230X-6-43-3</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Therapeutic approach to "downhill" esophageal varices bleeding due to superior vena cava syndrome in Behcet's disease: a case report Endoscopic findings on upper third of esophagus.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-230X-7-29-1</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Findings in patients with chronic intestinal dysmotility investigated by capsule endoscopy Erosion . Erosion in the small intestine, detected by capsule endoscopy in a patient with chronic intestinal dysmotility and large amounts of intestinal content.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-230X-7-29-2</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Findings in patients with chronic intestinal dysmotility investigated by capsule endoscopy Ulcer . Ulcer in the small intestine as seen by capsule endoscopy in a patient with chronic intestinal dysmotility.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2407-10-360-1</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Gorlin syndrome associated with small bowel carcinoma and mesenchymal proliferation of the gastrointestinal tract: case report and review of literature Endoscopy of upper GI-tract . Polyploid structure seen in the antrum.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2407-7-79-2</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Gastrointestinal stromal tumour of the duodenum in childhood: a rare case report Intra-operative push-endoscopy: GIST protusion into the duodenal lumen with mucosa ulcerated.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2474-9-78-7</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Soft tissue tenodesis of the long head of the biceps tendon associated to the Roman Bridge repair A shuttle passing through an anterior point of the rotator cuff and through the tenotomized long head of the biceps tendon.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2474-9-78-8</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Soft tissue tenodesis of the long head of the biceps tendon associated to the Roman Bridge repair All the sutures from the anteromedial anchor are passed through a single anterior point in the rotator cuff using the shuttle.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2482-11-14-1</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Severe gastric variceal haemorrhage due to splenic artery thrombosis and consecutive arterial bypass The upper gastrointestinal endoscopy showed preoperative thick submucous varices along a small ulcer, one clip in situ .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2482-4-15-4</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Pudendal nerve decompression in perineology : a case series Alcock's canal viewed from below like in the operating room (right side of a female cadaver): inferior rectal nerve (horizontal) showing the entrance of the canal.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1477-7800-3-1-1</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Breast papillomas: current management with a focus on a new diagnostic and therapeutic modality Mammary ductoscopy image showing intraductal papilloma.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1477-7819-3-11-2</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Spontaneous rupture of giant gastric stromal tumor into gastric lumen Upper endoscopy picture shows opening in the posterior part of the corpus with edematous margin with dissemination of serous fluid and necrotic material in to the stomach.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1477-7819-5-37-3</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Endoscopically assisted resection of a scapular osteochondroma causing snapping scapula syndrome Endoscopic image shows that the tumor was removed by use of a grasper.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1477-7819-7-9-2</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Minute ampullary carcinoid tumor with lymph node metastases: a case report and review of literature Endoscopy shows a slightly enlarged ampullary region, suggesting the existence of a submucosal tumor because the epithelium has a normal appearance .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1710-1492-6-14-1</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Acquired angioedema Capsule endoscopy showing bowel occlusion due to angioedema of the gastrointestinal mucosa in a patient with C1-INH deficiency suffering from acute abdominal pain .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1743-422X-3-6-1</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Epstein-barr virus induced cellular changes in nasal mucosa Nasal endoscopy: rounded neoplasm of inferior turbinate.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1749-7922-2-30-3</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Recurrent laryngeal nerve palsy due to impacted dental plate in the thoracic oesophagus: case report Dental plate impacted in oesophagus at endoscopy.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1749-7922-2-32-1</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Hematochezia in a patient with liver cirrhosis Endoscopic view of the rectum showing rectal varices, one of which demonstrates a red wheal consistent with recent bleeding.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1749-7922-2-32-2</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Hematochezia in a patient with liver cirrhosis Retroflexed view of rectum again showing the main varix with its bleeding point.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1749-8090-6-118-1</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Thoracoscopic resection of thoracic esophageal duplication cyst containing ectopic pancreatic tissue in adult Gastrointestinal endoscopy showed the esophageal diverticulum in the left side of middle thoracic esophagus, covered with columner epithlium (arrow) .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1750-1172-3-5-3</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Primary intestinal lymphangiectasia (Waldmann's disease) Capsule endoscopy (M2A, Given Imaging, Yoqneam, Israel): note the edematous aspect of the jejunum mucosa with whitish, swollen villi.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1752-1947-1-136-3</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Role of hemoclips in the management of acute bleeding from a gastric stromal tumor: a case report and review of the literature Repeat upper endoscopy 5 months after the episode of bleeding showed significant reduction of the tumor size and the previously identified ulcers were completely healed (arrow head).</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1752-1947-1-160-1</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Esophageal cancer in a young woman with bulimia nervosa: a case report Endoscopy . Shown is a small 10 mm ulcerated lesion at the GE junction (blue arrow) seen on endoscopy.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1752-1947-2-129-1</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Rare ileal localisation of angiolipoma presenting as chronic haemorrhage and severe anaemia: a case report Ileal polypoid neoformation shown by capsule endoscopy.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1752-1947-4-145-1</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Esophageal intramural pseudodiverticulosis characterized by barium esophagography: a case report Endoscopic image of the esophagus . The pseudodiverticular orifices appear as multiple erythematous macules on the surface of the esophagus.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1752-1947-5-110-2</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Gastrointestinal relapse of multiple myeloma and sustained response to lenalidomide: a case report Jejunal mass as seen on the upper gastrointestinal endoscopy .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1752-1947-5-233-1</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Human immunodeficiency virus infection and autoimmune hepatitis during highly active anti-retroviral treatment: a case report and review of the literature Laparoscopic image of the liver showing diffuse whitish-gray plaque without nodularity or cirrhosis .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1752-1947-5-306-1</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Adhesions due to peritoneal carcinomatosis caused by a renal carcinoma leading to mechanical gastric outlet obstruction: a case report Narrowing of lumen at upper endoscopy .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1752-1947-5-341-1</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Asymptomatic bronchial aspiration and prolonged retention of a capsule endoscope: a case report Capsule endoscopy . Capsule endoscopy view of the bronchial system.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1752-1947-5-544-3</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Boerhaave syndrome as a complication of colonoscopy preparation: a case report A small cylinder-shaped polyurethane sponge (sp) of dimensions 10  ×  40 mm was sewn to a gastric tube (tb) and placed by endoscopy at the suspected lesion and connected via tb with the VAC therapy unit at 125 mmHg of continuous suction .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1754-9493-3-23-1</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Management of synchronous adenocarcinoma of the esophago-gastric junction and ampulla of Vater: case report of a surgically challenging condition An upper gastrointestinal endoscopy showed irregular AGE Type II junctional tumour with a tongue of Barrett's esophagus .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1757-1626-0002-0000006198-003</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Simultaneous laparoscopic cholecystectomy and removal of an intrauterine device translocated to the right subdiaphragmal region: a case report The IUD  “ in situ ?  during laparoscopy.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1757-1626-0002-0000006199-001</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Hemangioma of penile urethra — treatment with simple transurethral excision: a case report Endoscopic view of the hemangioma of the penile urethra in the patient.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1757-1626-0002-0000006462-4</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Endoscopic resection of giant lipoma mimicking colonic neoplasm initially presenting with massive haemorrhage: a case report Endoclips were placed to approach the ulcer margins .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1757-1626-0002-0000007418-003</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Severe dysphagia due to a huge epiphrenic diverticulum: long-term treatment with balloon dilation and botulinum toxin injection: a case report The presence of blood is due to BTX injection.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1757-1626-0002-0000007975-001</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Transmural migration of a surgical compress into the stomach after splenectomy: a case report A mass compatible with a phytobezoar was observed in the duodenum via endoscopy.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1757-1626-0002-0000008000-003</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>An unusual presentation of Boerhaave Syndrome: a case report Endoscopy demonstrating region of tear proximal to esophago-gastric junction with no evidence of active haemorrhage.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1757-1626-0002-0000008093-007</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Esophageal granular cell tumor colliding with intramucosal adenocarcinoma: a case report Pseudopolyp created following endoscopic suction and band application visualized through Cook Endoscopy Duette ®  Multi-Band Mucosectomy Device.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1757-1626-0002-0000008541-006</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Simultaneous occurrence of hyperthyroidism and fistulizing Crohn ’ s disease complicated with intra-abdominal fistulas and abscess: a case report and review of the literature Colonoscopy. Endoscopic appearance of a fistulous tract opening in the proximal transverse colon near the hepatic flexure (continuous white arrow).</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1757-1626-1-164-2</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Laparoscopic management of an uncommon cause for right lower quadrant pain: A case report The infarcted omental segment being detached from the parietal wall using a suction-irrigation cannula.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1757-1626-1-235-1</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>An uncommon cause of lower gastrointestinal bleeding: a case report Endoscopic view of the carcinoid tumor.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1757-1626-1-251-1</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Arytenoid dislocation related to an uneventful endotracheal intubation: a case report On the 6 th  day after the operation, fiberoptic laryngoscopy was seen as anteromedial dislocation of the left arytenoid cartilage.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1757-1626-1-341-1</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Giant ileal inflammatory fibroid polyp causing small bowel obstruction: a case report and review of the literature Endoscopy image of a pedunculated polyp filling ileal lumen.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1757-1626-2-104-1</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Angiosarcoma of the nasal cavity: a case report Nasal endoscopy that shows a tumor in the left nasal wall .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1757-1626-2-159-1</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Ocular disorders as the prevailing manifestations of antiphospholipid syndrome: a case series RE fundus photography shows vascular occlusion and vitritis  (Case 1) .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1757-1626-2-16-2</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>A deceptive MRI appearance of the medial meniscus in a 14 year old boy: a case report Arthroscopic photograph showing normal medial meniscus .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1757-1626-2-189-1</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Metastatic Melanoma presenting 24 years after surgical resection: a case report and review of the literature Gastric Ulcer: Endoscopic picture of gastric metastatic melanoma .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1757-1626-2-189-2</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Metastatic Melanoma presenting 24 years after surgical resection: a case report and review of the literature Duodenal Ulcers: Endoscopic picture of duodenal metastatic melanoma .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1757-1626-2-9083-3</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Intramural duodenal hematoma and hemoperitoneum after endoscopic treatment in a patient with chronic renal failure on hemodialysis: a case report Follow-up endoscopy shows a near-total obstruction of the duodenal lumen by the hematoma .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1757-1626-2-9354-3</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Mucosa-associated lymphoid tissue lymphoma of the duodenum together with multiple intra-abdominal thromboses and hepatitis C virus infection: a case report Endoscopic findings of the descending part of the duodenum . Mucosa is observed edematous, fragile and granular; multiple small ulcerated lesions are also seen.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1757-1626-3-2-4</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Successful treatment of tracheal stenosis by rigid bronchoscopy and topical mitomycin C: a case report The appearance of the stenotic area 2 weeks after the procedure .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1757-1626-3-39-1</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Massive GI bleeding in a patient with 2 small AVMs in the small intestine: a case report Capsule endoscopy image showing an arteriovenous malformation in the small bowel at approximately 12 o'clock .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1758-2555-1-2-10</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>The results of arthroscopic anterior stabilisation of the shoulder using the bioknotless anchor system The anchor is inserted until the desired tension is achieved . The shuttle suture is then removed.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1758-2555-1-2-9</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>The results of arthroscopic anterior stabilisation of the shoulder using the bioknotless anchor system The BioKnotless anchor is gently tapped into the hole .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>cc2843-2</ID>
<CLASS>DVEN</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Innovations in technology for critical care medicine Bleeding from angiodysplasia in the small bowel.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1465-9921-6-98-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Mortality in GOLD stages of COPD and its dependence on symptoms of chronic bronchitis Flow chart of the study population.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1468-6708-5-11-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Early and long-term outcome of elective stenting of the infarct-related artery in patients with viability in the infarct-area: Rationale and design of the Viability-guided Angioplasty after acute Myocardial Infarction-trial (The VIAMI-trial) Flow chart</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2105-10-199-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>DOTcvpSB, a software toolbox for dynamic optimization in systems biology General scheme for the solution of a DO problem in DOTcvpSB . DOTcvpSB: solution scheme based on CVP for mixed-integer dynamic optimization problems.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2105-5-136-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>A combinational feature selection and ensemble neural network method for classification of gene expression data The whole flow chart</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2105-5-89-2</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>A double classification tree search algorithm for index SNP selection Flow chart of the algorithm.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2105-6-110-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Ab initio identification of putative human transcription factor binding sites by comparative genomics Flow-chart of the algorithm</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2105-6-184-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>A computational approach for identifying pathogenicity islands in prokaryotic genomes Flow chart of the algorithm.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2105-6-53-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Evolutionary sequence analysis of complete eukaryote genomes Flowchart of multigenome intersection approach (MIA). 1) Complete genomes are reciprocally compared against themselves and all other genomes with BLAST. 2) Pairwise ortholog clusters are identified using similarity scores and imported into a local database. 3) The intersection between genomes is determined by iteratively comparing sequence identification tags and retaining those clusters showing panorthology. 4) Additional genomes are added and checked as in the previous step. 5) Sequence data files are generated for evolutionary analysis.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2105-8-377-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Representing default knowledge in biomedical ontologies: application to the integration of anatomy and phenotype ontologies The main categories of the General Formal Ontology (GFO) as outlined in [14, p. 70]. The basic distinction of GFO relevant for this work relates to items and is between individuals and categories. Individuals are items that cannot be instantiated. Categories are items that can have instances and may be predicated of other entities. The instances of categories of first order are individuals, while higher-order categories have categories as instances. For all items, the  instance-of  relationship is a relation of major importance, linking items (including categories) to the categories of which they are an instance.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2105-9-S4-S6-3</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>RDFScape: Semantic Web meets Systems Biology Example of a visual query . The pattern shown represents the query: “ All the elements of type protein whose name contains the string  “ P53 ?  that are part of an interaction taking place in the nucleoplasm region ? . This pattern was generated while browsing the Homo sapiens Reactome export in Pathway Commons, by declaring as variable two of the elements. It presents several elements describing the structure of a pathway: these are from the BioPAX ontology (blue in the figure). The object of the CELLULAR-LOCATION property is a term defined in Reactome (in purple). Results of this query on the Reactome Homo sapiens ontology are presented in Table  1 . This query can be used both to map its results to an existing Cytoscape network, or to generate a new network from all possible occurrences of the relative pattern in the ontology.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2164-10-89-1</ID>
<CLASS>COMP</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Impact of breed and sex on porcine endocrine transcriptome: a bayesian biometrical analysis Dendrograms between breed z-scores for a subset of tissues . The breed z-score is a Bayesian standardized measure of expression level in that breed (see methods).</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2164-11-191-2</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Development of a SNP resource and a genetic linkage map for Atlantic cod ( Gadus morhua ) SNP validation from CGP panels 1 and 2 . Flowchart showing the output resulting from testing of the 3072 selected SNPs. The 1620 "predicted alleles" correspond to the set of validated SNPs.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2164-7-206-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>A high-density consensus map of barley linking DArT markers to SSR, RFLP and STS loci and agricultural traits Schematic outline of map-building strategies used in this study . Pilot maps were built for each of the ten populations separately to flip the phase of loci assigned to the wrong phase, to identify multi-locus markers, and to remove loci and lines with excessive numbers of singletons (apparent double crossovers). The quality-filtered datasets were then used to build seven 'component' maps for individual populations with sufficient numbers of lines and loci. The integrated dataset of all ten populations was used to build a consensus map. The quality of the locus order of the consensus map was evaluated by comparison against the order of loci in the component maps and a 'synthetic map' derived from the component maps.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2164-9-193-7</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Multiple expressed MHC class II loci in salmonids; details of one non-classical region in Atlantic salmon ( Salmo salar ) Phylogeny of teleost MHC class II beta sequences . Phylogenetic tree analysis by NJ method for full-length amino acid sequences. Consensus trees were based on 1000 bootstrap replications and reported with the bootstrap support values (in percent) indicated above the respective nodes. Sequence references are as follows: Sasa-DAB [GenBank:  CAD27784 ], Sasa-DBB [GenBank:  DY726096 ], Onmy-DAB [GenBank:  AAA79133 ], Onmy-DBB [GenBank:  AAD53026 ], Orla-DAB [GenBank:  BAA94279 ], Orla-DBB [GenBank:  BAA94280 ], Xima-DAB [GenBank:  AAC05652 ], Gaac-DAB [GenBank:  AAU01918 ], Gaac-DBB [GenBank:  AAU01920 ], Gaac-EST [Genbank:  DN681207 ], Dila-DAB [GenBank:  ABH09450 ], Fuhe-EST1 [GenBank:  CN976662 ], Fuhe-EST2 [GenBank:  CN984097 ], Taru-EST [GenBank:  CA846190 ], Icpu-DAB [GenBank:  AAB67871 ], Cyca-DAB [GenBank:  CAA64709 ], Dare-DAB [GenBank:  NP_571551 ], Dare-DCB [GenBank:  CAD56804 ], Dare-DDB [GenBank:  AAA87893 ], Dare-EST [Genbank:  CK126567 ], Pipr-EST1 [GenBank:  DT084791 ], Pipr-EST2 [GenBank:  DT351641 ], Pipr-EST3 [GenBank:  DT139435 ], Pipr-EST4 [GenBank:  DT355684 ], Ximu-DXB [GenBank:  AAS55041 ], Gici-DAB [GenBank:  AAF82681 ] and HLA_DRB1 [GenBank:  AAA59781 ].</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2229-9-78-10</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Agrobacterium rhizogenes -mediated transformation of  Superroot -derived  Lotus corniculatus  plants: a valuable tool for functional genomics A flowchart for  A. rhizogenes -mediated transformation of  L. corniculatus  cv.  Superroot .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2296-11-67-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Patients presenting with somatic complaints in general practice: depression, anxiety and somatoform disorders are frequent and associated with psychosocial stressors Flow chart .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2296-4-7-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Quality of life and metabolic status in mildly depressed women with type 2 diabetes treated with paroxetine: A single-blind randomised placebo controlled trial Flow chart of trial participants.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-230X-10-40-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Prevalence of liver fibrosis and risk factors in a general population using non-invasive biomarkers (FibroTest) Flow sheet of subjects included .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2318-11-48-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>[Cost]effectiveness of withdrawal of fall-risk increasing drugs versus conservative treatment in older fallers: design of a multicenter randomized controlled trial (IMPROveFALL-study) Flow chart .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2318-2-1-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Frailty, fitness and late-life mortality in relation to chronological and biological age Population sample flow chart.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2318-5-11-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Design and pilot results of a single blind randomized controlled trial of systematic demand-led home visits by nurses to frail elderly persons in primary care [ISRCTN05358495] Flow chart PIKO.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2326-8-1-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Safety of intramuscular influenza vaccine in patients receiving oral anticoagulation therapy: a single blinded multi-centre randomized controlled clinical trial Flow chart</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2334-4-18-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Ofloxacin plus Rifampicin versus Doxycycline plus Rifampicin in the treatment of brucellosis: a randomized clinical trial [ISRCTN11871179] Flow chart of the patients in the study.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2377-10-110-1</ID>
<CLASS>COMP</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Charting the progression of disability in parkinson disease: study protocol for a prospective longitudinal cohort study Flow sheet of Study Procedures . Abbreviations: UAB = University of Alabama at Birmingham, MDS-UPDRS = Movement Disorders Society-Unified Parkinson Disease Rating Scale, FOG-Q = Freezing of Gait Questionnaire, PDQ-39 = Parkinson Disease Questionnaire - 39, PASE = Physical Activity Scale for the Elderly.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2407-6-251-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>A prospective study to assess the value of MMP-9 in improving the appropriateness of urgent referrals for colorectal cancer Research plan and study design.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2431-11-77-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>The impact of different doses of vitamin A supplementation on male and female mortality. A randomised trial from Guinea-Bissau Flow chart .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2458-10-348-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>A pilot study combining individual-based smoking cessation counseling, pharmacotherapy, and dental hygiene intervention Flow chart .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2458-11-252-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>GET WELL: an automated surveillance system for gaining new epidemiological knowledge Flow chart . A flow chart of GET WELL.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2458-6-124-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Effectiveness of a Minimal Intervention for Stress-related mental disorders with Sick leave (MISS); study protocol of a cluster randomised controlled trial in general practice [ISRCTN43779641] 'Flow chart'.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2458-9-381-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>The usefulness of a free self-test for screening albuminuria in the general population: a cross-sectional survey Flow chart of participants .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2458-9-88-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>The incidence of co-morbidities related to obesity and overweight: A systematic review and meta-analysis Flowchart of article distribution for all diseases .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2466-9-15-3</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>ICE COLD ERIC  –  International collaborative effort on chronic obstructive lung disease: exacerbation risk index cohorts  –  Study protocol for an international COPD cohort study flow chart .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2474-10-139-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Expectations, perceptions, and physiotherapy predict prolonged sick leave in subacute low back pain Flowchart of participation and follow up data .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2474-11-212-2</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>An educational approach based on a non-injury model compared with individual symptom-based physical training in chronic LBP. A pragmatic, randomised trial with a one-year follow-up The patients' flow throughout the study . EDUC = educational approach.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2474-11-69-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Use of platelet rich plasma to treat plantar fasciitis: design of a multi centre randomized controlled trial Flow chart .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2474-12-14-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Protocol for Shoulder function training reducing musculoskeletal pain in shoulder and neck: a randomized controlled trial Flow chart .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2474-5-39-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Conservative treatment in patients with an acute lumbosacral radicular syndrome: design of a randomised clinical trial [ISRCTN68857256] Flow chart of the LRS trial.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2474-6-18-2</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>A 2-year prospective study of patient-relevant outcomes in patients operated on for knee osteoarthritis with tibial osteotomy Flow chart of the study design.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2474-6-8-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Prolonged conservative treatment or 'early' surgery in sciatica caused by a lumbar disc herniation: rationale and design of a randomized trial [ISRCT 26872154] Flow chart of the Sciatica Trial</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2474-8-112-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Effect of an education and activation programme on functional limitations and patient-perceived recovery in acute and sub-acute shoulder complaints  –  a randomised clinical trial Flow chart.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2482-10-24-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Ten-year audit of Lichtenstein hernioplasty under local anaesthesia performed by surgical residents Flow chart of the study .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2482-3-2-5</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Surgical physiology of inguinal hernia repair - a study of 200 cases Flow chart.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1472-6793-7-3-2</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Regulatory network of inflammation downstream of proteinase-activated receptors Participation of PAR1-dependent genes in canonical pathways . The experimental datasets of PAR1-dependent genes was used to query the Ingenuity Pathways Analysis [IPA] and overlaid to canonical pathways.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1472-6874-5-4-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>A cluster randomized controlled trial of a behavioral intervention to facilitate the development and implementation of clinical practice guidelines in Latin American maternity hospitals: the Guidelines Trial: Study protocol [ISRCTN82417627] Trial Profile</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1472-6874-9-24-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Protocol for Physiotherapy OR Tvt Randomised Efficacy Trial (PORTRET): a multicentre randomised controlled trial to assess the cost-effectiveness of the tension free vaginal tape versus pelvic floor muscle training in women with symptomatic moderate to severe stress urinary incontinence Flow chart .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1472-6882-9-24-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Mindfulness for irritable bowel syndrome: protocol development for a controlled clinical trial Overall Design and Subject Flow .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1472-6920-3-2-2</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Randomised controlled trial of a theoretically grounded tailored intervention to diffuse evidence-based public health practice [ISRCTN23257060] Flow chart</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1472-6920-9-35-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>The effect of a brief social intervention on the examination results of UK medical students: a cluster randomised controlled trial CONSORT flow diagram showing the study profile .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1472-6947-10-9-2</ID>
<CLASS>COMP</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Regression tree construction by bootstrap: Model search for DRG-systems applied to Austrian health-data Two different trees constructed by bumping from the HDG0502 data. The two trees have different split points and variables, but have very similar predictive accuracy.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1472-6947-9-S1-S4-10</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Automated ventricular systems segmentation in brain CT images by combining low-level segmentation and high-level template matching Diagram of protrusion detection . The interior edge of the skull is extracted based on the intensity. Then by viewing the extracted edge as a function curve versus the horizontal coordinate of the image, the protrusion is the local minimal point of the function curve.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1472-6947-9-S1-S7-1</ID>
<CLASS>COMP</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Measuring the effect of commuting on the performance of the Bayesian Aerosol Release Detector Schematic representation of the simulation and detection studies . Part (a): simulation study; part (b): detection study</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1472-6963-10-112-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Effectiveness and efficiency of primary care based case management for chronic diseases: rationale and design of a systematic review and meta-analysis of randomized and non-randomized trials [CRD32009100316] The principle case management process . The figure shows the principle process of varying case management approaches. It consists of "case finding" and "individualized assessment" followed by "planning" different "actions" which are "monitored" and/or re-assessed with implications on future plans and actions.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1472-6963-4-29-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Recruiting pregnant smokers for a placebo-randomised controlled trial of nicotine replacement therapy Flow Chart of Study Participation</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1472-6963-4-30-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>A randomised controlled trial to determine the effect on response of including a lottery incentive in health surveys [ISRCTN32203485] Questionnaire response rates</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1472-6963-5-38-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Intermediate care: for better or worse? Process evaluation of an intermediate care model between a university hospital and a residential home Flow chart</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1472-6963-5-52-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Effect on survey response rate of hand written versus printed signature on a covering letter: randomised controlled trial [ISRCTN67566265] Flow chart of study participants.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1472-6963-7-104-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>The structure of quality systems is important to the process and outcome, an empirical study of 386 hospital departments in Sweden The proposed model . Structure is related to process and outcome. Process is related to outcome.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1472-6963-7-25-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Comparing health system performance assessment and management approaches in the Netherlands and Ontario, Canada Conceptual Framework for Dutch National Health System Performance.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1472-6963-8-189-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Initial impact and cost of a nationwide population screening campaign for diabetes in Brazil: A follow up study Population estimates for the initial impact of the National Campaign to Detect Diabetes Mellitus. Brazil, 2001.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1475-2875-7-123-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Impact of intermittent preventive treatment with sulphadoxine-pyrimethamine targeting the transmission season on the incidence of clinical malaria in children in Mali Flow Chart.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1475-2883-5-12-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Delimitation of lymphatic filariasis transmission risk areas: a geo-environmental approach Conceptual Frame for LF Transmission.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1475-2891-7-28-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>An increase of cereal intake as an approach to weight reduction in children is effective only when accompanied by nutrition education: a randomized controlled trial Flow-chart.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1475-2891-8-7-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>A natural seaweed derived mineral supplement (Aquamin F) for knee osteoarthritis: A randomised, placebo controlled pilot study Trial flow chart .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1476-511X-5-7-2</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Effects of conjugated linoleic acid and exercise on bone mass in young male Balb/C mice Schematic Representation of the Possible Pathways Involved in the Action of CLA on Bone Mass. a = decrease bone resorption; b = increase bone formation.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1477-7525-3-4-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>The influence of demographic factors and health-related quality of life on treatment satisfaction in patients with gastroesophageal reflux disease treated with esomeprazole Flow chart</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1477-7525-8-148-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Psychometric properties of the Brief Pain Inventory among patients with osteoarthritis undergoing total hip replacement surgery Flow chart .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1477-7525-8-35-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Effects of mode of administration (MOA) on the measurement properties of the EORTC QLQ-C30: a randomized study Results of Patient accrual and randomization .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1477-7525-8-94-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Cross-cultural validity of four quality of life scales in persons with spinal cord injury Overview of the four Rasch-based strategies applied to account for the weaknesses in the metric properties of the four quality of life instruments post-hoc .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1478-7547-8-1-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Giving tranexamic acid to reduce surgical bleeding in sub-Saharan Africa: an economic evaluation Possible effects of administering TXA .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1479-5868-3-23-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Moms in motion: a group-mediated cognitive-behavioral physical activity intervention Flow diagram of participant randomization and follow up data collection . Figure 1 shows the process of participant inclusion/exclusion and randomization into the intervention treatment arms and subsequent follow up data collection. The figure should be read from top to bottom.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1479-5868-4-47-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>The cost-effectiveness of a school-based overweight program Flow Chart.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1479-5868-6-26-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Determinants of participation in worksite health promotion programmes: a systematic review Flow chart .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1741-7015-2-6-2</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Vasectomy by ligation and excision, with or without fascial interposition: a randomized controlled trial [ISRCTN77781689] Participant disposition flow chart</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1741-7015-8-75-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>How large are the nonspecific effects of acupuncture? A meta-analysis of randomized controlled trials Flow chart .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1742-4690-2-18-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>BioAfrica's HIV-1 Proteomics Resource: Combining protein data with bioinformatics tools Site map of BioAfrica's HIV-1 Proteomics Resource, showing the separation of Beginner's and the Advanced area of the website, along with all major subject headings.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1742-4755-5-10-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Water aerobics in pregnancy: cardiovascular response, labor and neonatal outcomes Flow chart of the study.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1742-4755-5-4-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>ICPD to MDGs: Missing links and common grounds Expected outcomes of working on common grounds between ICPD and MDGs.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1743-8977-7-27-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Cardiovascular and inflammatory effects of intratracheally instilled ambient dust from Augsburg, Germany, in spontaneously hypertensive rats (SHRs) The figure illustrates the rationale of experimental study evolving from the epidemiological findings .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1745-6215-10-20-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Rationale, design and methodology of a double-blind, randomized, placebo-controlled study of escitalopram in prevention of Depression in Acute Coronary Syndrome (DECARD) flow chart .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1745-6215-10-4-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>The impact of iron supplementation efficiency in female blood donors with a decreased ferritin level and no anaemia. Rationale and design of a randomised controlled trial: a study protocol flow chart .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1745-6215-12-154-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Exercise Training in Pregnancy for obese women (ETIP): study protocol for a randomised controlled trial Flow-chart .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1745-6215-12-221-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>The chronic care for age-related macular degeneration study (CHARMED): Study protocol for a randomized controlled trial Flow chart .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1745-6215-12-230-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Alzheimer's disease - input of vitamin D with mEmantine assay (AD-IDEA trial): study protocol for a randomized controlled trial Trial flow chart . Flow chart of the Trial Study.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1745-6215-7-11-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Protocol for the 'e-Nudge trial': a randomised controlled trial of electronic feedback to reduce the cardiovascular risk of individuals in general practice [ISRCTN64828380] Search algorithm to identify those most likely to benefit from cardiovascular prevention based on recent risk variable values. Definitions for terms in inverted commas are given in the appendix along with justification of thresholds and search protocol.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1745-6215-7-23-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Sub-vastus approach versus the medial parapatellar approach in primary total knee: a randomised controlled trial [ISRCTN44544446] Flow Chart.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1746-4811-1-9-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Combining metal oxide affinity chromatography (MOAC) and selective mass spectrometry for robust identification of  in vivo  protein phosphorylation sites Proposed strategy for robust identification of serine/threonine phosphorylation in plants. In case of low stoichiometry as for the  in vivo  situation enrichment of phosphoproteins is necessary. To cope with this a novel enrichment procedure called metaloxide affinity chromatography (MOAC) is used in the strategy [18]. The whole approach is applicable to identify phosphorylation sites out of complex samples. The library of  in vivo  sites may be used for screening of protein phosphorylation dynamics using triple-quadruple mass spectrometry [6] .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1747-597X-4-12-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Use of nicotine substitute prescribed at hourly plus ab libitum intake or ad libitum for heavy smokers willing to quit: a randomized controlled trial Flow Chart .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1748-5908-6-53-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Still too little qualitative research to shed light on results from reviews of effectiveness trials: A case study of a Cochrane review on the use of lay health workers Flow chart .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1752-0509-2-52-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>A computational analysis of protein-protein interaction networks in neurodegenerative diseases Retrieval and representation of each disease network.  The differentially expressed genes in MS or AD using blood or brain tissue were obtained from published DNA array studies. The corresponding protein (seed-protein) for each differentially expressed gene was identified in public databases (STRING). The network in which such proteins were embedded was built by retrieving the first neighbor of each protein in the protein-protein interaction database available at the STRING database.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1752-0509-2-64-3</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Integrated modeling and experimental approach for determining transcription factor profiles from fluorescent reporter data K-means clustering algorithm used for identifying cell regions in fluorescence images.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1752-0509-3-117-8</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Flux-sum analysis: a metabolite-centric approach for understanding the metabolic network Summary of metabolite classification . The numbers of metabolites in each category is shown in brackets. The abbreviations "E" and "NE" denote essential and nonessential metabolites respectively. "AC","BC", "CC" and "AE", "BE", "CE" refer to the types of metabolites identified in flux-sum intensification and attenuation analyses respectively.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1755-7682-3-22-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Statins and clinical outcome of acute ischemic stroke: a systematic review Flow diagram of included studies .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1755-8794-1-61-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>An expression meta-analysis of predicted microRNA targets identifies a diagnostic signature for lung cancer A flow diagram outlines selection of 13 human lung cancer databases used in this study . This diagram does not include the 14 th  dataset GSE2514 in Table 1 that is a mouse gene expression dataset and was not used to calculate the accuracy of prediction in the meta-analysis. DB, database.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1757-7241-18-6-2</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>A review of ureteral injuries after external trauma Ureteral trauma algorithm .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1758-2652-12-1-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Survey of physician knowledge regarding antiretroviral medications in hospitalized HIV-infected patients Flow chart .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1758-2652-12-8-1</ID>
<CLASS>GFLO</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Medication diaries do not improve outcomes with highly active antiretroviral therapy in Kenyan children: a randomized clinical trial Flow chart summarizing subject flow .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2105-4-7-2</ID>
<CLASS>GMAT</CLASS>
<CAPTION>A format for databasing and comparison of AFLP fingerprint profiles Formula for Rubberband and Spring energy, Er, Es and E are rubberband energy, spring energy and potential energy, respectively. x is the displacement and k r  and k s  are proportionality constants.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2105-5-113-7</ID>
<CLASS>GMAT</CLASS>
<CAPTION>MUSCLE: a multiple sequence alignment method with reduced time and space complexity Additive profiles.  The profile functions in MUSCLE require amino acid frequencies for each column. Here we show the alignment of two profiles X and Y, giving a new profile Z. Note that the count  n Z i  for amino acid  i  in a given column of Z is the sum of the counts in the child profiles, i.e.  n Z i  =  n X i  +  n Y i . In terms of frequencies, this becomes  f  Z i  =  N X f  X i  / N Z  +  N Y f  Y i / N Z , where  N X ,  N Y ,  N Z  are the number of sequences in X, Y and Z respectively. Therefore, given a suitable sequence weighting scheme, it is possible to compute frequencies in Z from the frequencies in X and Y. This avoids the step of building an explicit multiple alignment for Z in order to compute frequencies, as done in CLUSTALW and MAFFT.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2105-5-166-3</ID>
<CLASS>GMAT</CLASS>
<CAPTION>A probabilistic model for the evolution of RNA structure An SCFG with nonterminals { L } and terminals  Ω  for generating the equilibrium distribution over TKF91 sequences. Here  X  ∈   Ω  is a generic terminal symbol.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2202-6-4-11</ID>
<CLASS>GMAT</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Treatment of trigeminal ganglion neurons in vitro with NGF, GDNF or BDNF: effects on neuronal survival, neurochemical properties and TRPV1-mediated neuropeptide secretion Equation used to normalize CGRP release . "No GF" refers to no growth factor controls and "GF condition" refers to any given growth factor treated condition</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2288-3-22-2</ID>
<CLASS>GMAT</CLASS>
<CAPTION>How many repeated measures in repeated measures designs? Statistical issues for comparative trials Derivation of statistical formula</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2377-8-23-2</ID>
<CLASS>GMAT</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Carotid bruits as predictor for carotid stenoses detected by ultrasonography: an observational study Calculating Positive Likelihood Percentage (PLP) using sensitivity and specificity . Inserting the formula for calculating the positive likelihood ratio using sensitivity and specificity into the newly formed formula for calculating PLP. Then the formula is simplified in two steps.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2377-8-23-3</ID>
<CLASS>GMAT</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Carotid bruits as predictor for carotid stenoses detected by ultrasonography: an observational study Calculating Negative Likelihood Percentage (NLP) using sensitivity and specificity . Inserting the formula for calculating the negative likelihood ratio using sensitivity and specificity into the newly formed formula for calculating NLP. Then the formula is simplified in one step.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2393-9-1-3</ID>
<CLASS>GMAT</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Design of FitFor2 study: the effects of an exercise program on insulin sensitivity and plasma glucose levels in pregnant women at high risk for gestational diabetes Formula . A: lifted weight; B: percentage of intensity.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2474-8-125-4</ID>
<CLASS>GMAT</CLASS>
<CAPTION>The PRICE study (Protection Rest Ice Compression Elevation): design of a randomised controlled trial comparing standard versus cryokinetic ice applications in the management of acute ankle sprain [ISRCTN13903946] Formula used for sample size calculations.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-5945-6-10-23</ID>
<CLASS>GMAT</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Mohs math  –  where the error hides Mathematical proof, mathematical formula of predicted error.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-5945-6-10-33</ID>
<CLASS>GMAT</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Mohs math  –  where the error hides Mathematical formula of predicted viewable margin.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1472-6963-5-51-1</ID>
<CLASS>GMAT</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Predictors of failed attendances in a multi-specialty outpatient centre using electronic databases Predicted probability equation for appointment failure derived from the multiple logistic regression model.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1475-925X-3-20-1</ID>
<CLASS>GMAT</CLASS>
<CAPTION>A mathematical model for the burden of diabetes and its complications The mathematical model</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1476-072X-7-35-12</ID>
<CLASS>GMAT</CLASS>
<CAPTION>The geosimulation of West Nile virus propagation: a multi-agent and climate sensitive tool for risk management in public health (a) Differential equations of Wonham's mathematical model [ 16 ] , and (b) the new equations of the proposed model [ 18 ].</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1532-429X-11-47-2</ID>
<CLASS>GMAT</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Diffusion MR tractography of the heart Mathematical basis of DSI tractography . DSI tractograms are 6 dimensional images, containing 3 dimensions of image (x, y, z) space and 3 dimensions of q-space. The generated streamlines are tangent to the ODF vector field at all points, as shown in equation 4.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1746-6148-4-42-2</ID>
<CLASS>GMAT</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Estimating the temporal and spatial risk of bluetongue related to the incursion of infected vectors into Switzerland R 0  equation . Equation for calculating the Basic Reproductive number, circled I, II, and III to represent the different components.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1752-0509-2-91-1</ID>
<CLASS>GMAT</CLASS>
<CAPTION>ALC: automated reduction of rule-based models Types of interactions between processes . Reactions are indicated by arrows. The reaction rate for each reaction is denoted as  d i  and parameterized by  k i  and  k - i . A) Visualization of a graded interaction between the processes of  L  binding and  D  phosphorylation. The same scheme can be taken to demonstrate non-interacting processes. For non-interacting processes the parameter restrictions  k 1  =  k 3 ,  k -1  =  k -3 ,  k 2  =  k 4  and  k -2  =  k -4  hold. B) Visualization of an all-or-none interaction between the processes of binding site phosphorylation and  E  binding.  E  can only bind to phosphorylated sites, while the dephosphorylation of  D  is only possible in the absence of a bound effector. C) The cyclic reaction scheme degenerates to a reaction chain, as the species  D [0, 0,  E ] does not exist. In this case, the notation can be simplified by describing binding site phosphorylation and  E  binding as modifications of the same site.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1752-4458-4-26-1</ID>
<CLASS>GMAT</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Public perception of mental health in Iraq Method of Sample size calculation . where, n = sample size. N = population size. Z = Standard normal distribution (set at1.96 corresponding to a confidence level of 95%). p = Probability of success (0.5). q = Probability of failure (0.5). e = Precision level = (0.07)</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1756-0381-2-8-3</ID>
<CLASS>GMAT</CLASS>
<CAPTION>3PFDB - A database of Best Representative PSSM Profiles (BRPs) of Protein Families generated using a novel data mining approach 3PFDB - Coverage analysis formula .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>gb-2004-5-7-r50-5</ID>
<CLASS>GMAT</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Detecting DNA regulatory motifs by incorporating positional trends in information content Update formulae for motif parameters using model with change points. Updates in M-step depend on the functional form of  f  ( L 1  or  L 2 ). See details in Figure 4. See [35] for solutions to the cubic equation.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2105-10-S1-S9-4</ID>
<CLASS>GPLI</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Sorting by reversals, block interchanges, tandem duplications, and deletions The algorithm . The algorithm in pseudocode.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2105-11-96-15</ID>
<CLASS>GPLI</CLASS>
<CAPTION>SING: Subgraph search In Non-homogeneous Graphs Filtering . Filtering algorithm.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2105-12-S10-S12-6</ID>
<CLASS>GPLI</CLASS>
<CAPTION>An improved border detection in dermoscopy images for density based clustering Algorithm FDBLD</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2105-5-25-5</ID>
<CLASS>GPLI</CLASS>
<CAPTION>A web services choreography scenario for interoperating bioinformatics applications BPEL Choreography  An extract from the BPEL file describing the choreography of GetHAPI and GetUMLS web services.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2105-6-5-5</ID>
<CLASS>GPLI</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Critical evaluation of the JDO API for the persistence and portability requirements of complex biological databases Example of JDO file . This file is used to define the persistent classes that are used in SigPath to represent end-users. Four persistent classes are shown: Address, Affiliation, User and UserRole. The< field>  element can be used to refer to specific fields of persistent classes (such as the username field of class User on this example). The userRoles field is described to be a collection that contains elements of type UserRole. Elements called< extension>  make it possible to provide vendor specific directives, such as to define indices on a persistent field.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2105-6-54-8</ID>
<CLASS>GPLI</CLASS>
<CAPTION>In silico  microdissection of microarray data from heterogeneous cell populations The two-step optimization algorithm . Details of the two-step algorithm used for the optimization problem shown in Equation (4).</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2105-6-76-7</ID>
<CLASS>GPLI</CLASS>
<CAPTION>An Entropy-based gene selection method for cancer classification using microarray data Greedy Algorithm.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2105-7-17-4</ID>
<CLASS>GPLI</CLASS>
<CAPTION>An approach for clustering gene expression data with error information CORE algorithm.  The figure provides a description of the CORE algorithm.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2105-7-S1-S3-2</ID>
<CLASS>GPLI</CLASS>
<CAPTION>PepDist: A New Framework for Protein-Peptide Binding Prediction based on Learning Peptide Distance Functions The  PepDist  framework.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2105-8-136-1</ID>
<CLASS>GPLI</CLASS>
<CAPTION>An adaptive bin framework search method for a beta-sheet protein homopolymer model High-level outline of the main body of the Bin Framework Search Method . Outline of the main body of the Bin Framework Search Method.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2105-8-58-3</ID>
<CLASS>GPLI</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Sequence similarity is more relevant than species specificity in probabilistic backtranslation Core EasyBack algorithm . Description of EasyBack algorithm.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2105-9-344-9</ID>
<CLASS>GPLI</CLASS>
<CAPTION>An enhanced partial order curve comparison algorithm and its application to analyzing protein folding trajectories The merging algorithm.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2105-9-S11-S11-1</ID>
<CLASS>GPLI</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Automatic inference of indexing rules for MEDLINE ALEPH  Algorithm.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2105-9-S6-S8-6</ID>
<CLASS>GPLI</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Dimension reduction with redundant gene elimination for tumor classification The RELIC algorithm.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1471-2164-12-S2-S9-5</ID>
<CLASS>GPLI</CLASS>
<CAPTION>bNEAT: a Bayesian network method for detecting epistatic interactions in genome-wide association studies the bNEAT algorithm</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1472-6947-5-30-5</ID>
<CLASS>GPLI</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Automation of a problem list using natural language processing Example CDA document.  XML Clinical Document Architecture version of the analyzed document.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1472-6963-10-125-2</ID>
<CLASS>GPLI</CLASS>
<CAPTION>A toolkit for incorporating genetics into mainstream medical services: Learning from service development pilots in England A Toolkit for developing services for patients with or at risk of genetic conditions . The full Toolkit with customisable resources is available online at  http://www.geneticseducation.nhs.uk .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1746-4811-2-2-5</ID>
<CLASS>GPLI</CLASS>
<CAPTION>A petal breakstrength meter for Arabidopsis abscission studies Perl script findforces.pl used to facilitate extraction of petal breakstrength values from a folder of petal breakstrength assay text capture files.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1748-7188-1-11-4</ID>
<CLASS>GPLI</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Inverse bifurcation analysis: application to simple gene systems Algorithm APPLYF.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1748-7188-1-20-5</ID>
<CLASS>GPLI</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Reconstructing protein structure from solvent exposure using tabu search Algorithm 1.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1748-7188-1-20-6</ID>
<CLASS>GPLI</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Reconstructing protein structure from solvent exposure using tabu search Algorithm 2.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1748-7188-1-21-6</ID>
<CLASS>GPLI</CLASS>
<CAPTION>EXMOTIF: efficient structured motif extraction EXMOTIF Algorithm.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1748-7188-1-22-10</ID>
<CLASS>GPLI</CLASS>
<CAPTION>SMOTIF: efficient structured pattern and profile motif search SMOTIF Algorithm.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1748-7188-2-15-3</ID>
<CLASS>GPLI</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Efficient and accurate P-value computation for Position Weight Matrices Algorithm ScoreDistribution.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1748-7188-2-15-4</ID>
<CLASS>GPLI</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Efficient and accurate P-value computation for Position Weight Matrices Algorithm FastPvalue.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>1756-0381-2-9-2</ID>
<CLASS>GPLI</CLASS>
<CAPTION>A biclustering algorithm based on a Bicluster Enumeration Tree: application to DNA microarray data BiMine  algorithm .</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>IJBI2009-156234.alg1</ID>
<CLASS>GPLI</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Segmentation of Striatal Brain Structures from High Resolution PET Images Graph partition algorithm (Weighted Kernel  k -means). This algorithm assigns the voxel  a i  to the cluster  π c  if the cluster  π c  minimizes the distance function from point 2 [ 7 ].</CAPTION>
</Figure>
<Figure>
<ID>IJBI2010-650298.alg.001</ID>
<CLASS>GPLI</CLASS>
<CAPTION>Qualitative Simulation of Photon Transport in Free Space Based on Monte Carlo Method and Its Parallel Implementation Uniform framework for MC-based photon transport model.</CAPTION>
</Figure>
</trainFigures>
